<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
              <objects>
              <CompanyID>2,1000000002,30225</CompanyID>
              <VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>382479</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>03/01/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=382479&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>New York</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>NY</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY>True</JOB_SALARY>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>$40,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>$60,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Full Time</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Tech Lead - .Net - MVC</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>* 6+ years experience with product development and architecture of consumer software and applications. * Proven experience working with latest technologies such as ASP.Net MVC, AngularJS, elasticsearch, MongoDB and RabbitMQ * Expert knowledge of agile, design and enterprise patterns. * Strong working experience of .NET, MVC with C#. * Expert knowledge of object oriented programming. * Knowledge of domain driven design. * Knowledge of test driven development. * Knowledge of SQL Server development and database design. * Knowledge of UI patterns. * Familiarity with source control, build processes, and continuous delivery * Experience guiding, coaching, and developing with other engineers * Must possess a solid business sense to analyze IT viability and strategic vision * A wide breadth of technical expertise preferred TMP Worldwide is an Equal Opportunity and Affirmative Action Employer, M/F/D/V.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>Up to 500 Miles</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>Overview: Innovative strategies. Proactive thinking. Comprehensive know-how. That's what we expect from a Tech Lead at TMP. Here, you'll be part of a fiercely collaborative technology team charged with creating digital solutions that are transforming the way employers and job seekers connect. That means contributing to high-traffic websites for a broad range of high-profile companies. Developing next-generation applications and products for some of the most recognized brands in the world. And actively supporting our diverse suite of best-in-class technologies. All this in an environment that constantly challenges you to push beyond boundaries and enhance your expertise&#x2014;with the support of a global team of industry experts. Sound like a fit for your talent and passion? Read on. Responsibilities: * This is a hands - on .NET development position * Work with latest technologies such as ASP.NET MVC, Entity Framework, AngularJS, RabbitMQ, elasticsearch, Redis, MongoDB * Research and recommend the implementation of new technology or technical tools to improve system performance, stability, development process. * Make recommendations as appropriate to ensure maximum stability and minimum downtime. * Contribute to overall technical strategy and development direction. Provide leadership on engineering aspects including design, analysis, testing and implementation. * Conduct and/or participate in formal and informal, internal and external technology presentations and reviews. * Oversee and develop next generation web applications and products. * Participate in all phases of the software engineering life cycle * Provide technical troubleshooting and debug support. * Develop and implement new products and provide information and support when required. * Evaluate new design proposals, investigate and recommend solutions and process improvements that deliver greater efficiency or performance benefits. * Ensure that necessary technical documentation is maintained in an appropriate manner To learn more about TMP Software Development and what we are working on- check out these links: https://www.tmp.com/tmp-technology-jobs Stack Overflow page: https://careers.stackoverflow.com/company/tmp-worldwide</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>377947</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/29/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=377947&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>New York</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>NY</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Human Resources &amp; Recruiting Coordinator</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>REQUIREMENTS: &#x2022; Bachelor&#x2019;s degree required &#x2022; 1-2 years HR experience/ 1-2 in Recruiting &#x2022; Previous administrative and scheduling experience in a fast paced office environment preferred &#x2022; Exposure to dealing with confidential and sensitive information required &#x2022; Working knowledge of HR practices and legalities to hiring a plus &#x2022; Outstanding organizational and follow-through skills. Strict attention to detail is a must &#x2022; Excellent interpersonal skills. Highly visible position &#x2022; Very strong computer skills. *Outlook/SharePoint skills must be excellent &#x2022; High level of resourcefulness and strong team player &#x2022; Ability to multi-task is essential, with a keen sense of priorities and sense of urgency &#x2022; Solid communication skills both written and verbal We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>The Human Resources Coordinator contributes to the goals of the Human Resources department by providing efficient and high level assistance in the administration of the day-to-day operations, functions and duties of the department. Responsibilities: &#x2022; Ensure all employee files are complete and in compliance including making photocopies, faxing and other clerical functions as needed &#x2022; Assist with all HR reporting and metrics data &#x2022; Ability to answer HR questions and provide guidance to employees on HR inquiries &#x2022; Prepare and issue official HR documentation as directed (i.e., employment verification letters) &#x2022; Assist with the new hire onboarding process including document collection background check reviewing and references checks &#x2022; Updating job descriptions and org charts as needed &#x2022; Assist in the coordination of various programs: corporate events, employee engagement events &#x2022; Understand and communicate company policies to employees &#x2022; Responsible for recruitment of all entry-level positions &#x2022; Responsible for coordination of all candidates from resume review &amp; disposition, to phone screen interviews, to scheduling in-person interview &#x2022; Work with Talent Acquisition Manger to complete background and reference checks on all candidates prior to hire &#x2022; Coordinate and schedule all internal recruitment meetings including recruitment team, hiring and hiring managers &#x2022; Manage the Internship Program &#x2022; Act as Internal Communications liaison to use existing templates, online tools and brand guidelines to produce internal emails, social content updates, and company calendar management</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>374378</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/29/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=374378&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>New York</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>NY</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Talent Acquisition &#x2013; People Development Manager</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>* Bachelor&#x2019;s degree * 5+ years&#x2019; experience in talent acquisition, recruitment operations or project management experience a must. * Creative problem solver with the demonstrated ability to provide pragmatic solutions to complex recruitment and retention issues. * Demonstrated ability to collaborate with internal clients (e.g., HR, hiring managers and department heads) and external partners. * Highly motivated with a &#x201c;sales focused&#x201d; spirit and a passion for working in a fast paced environment. * A willingness to roll up sleeves and undertake any and all recruitment/retention improvement projects. We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>This position will play an integral role within our organization to provide support to HR and business partners to implement key programs and processes related to talent acquisition, employee retention and recruitment marketing. This individual will play a lead role in evaluating, piloting and deploying marketing, technology and branding solutions to attract and retain the best talent. Responsibilities: * Revise and improve the interview process and hiring decision making process by utilizing data and feedback from hiring managers and candidates. * Work with Management team to develop and deploy our comprehensive Recruitment Marketing Program. * Project Manage our Recruitment Marketing activities. * Work closely with HR and department heads to develop effective metrics necessary to analyze the retention rates across the Company (with a goal of increasing employee retention and improving employee engagement). * Responsible for career path development for employees. * Enhance candidate onboarding process and experience. * Document and analyze data (e.g., time to fill open positions, success rate of job sourcing methods and number of applications) in order to improve recruitment performance. * Manage job posting metrics, develop a retention program, revise job descriptions and monitor employee satisfaction via social media. * Assist with execution of social media campaigns related to enhancing recruitment initiatives. * Work closely with HR Director and Talent Acquisition Manager to improve employee development and training programs. * Ensure all HR systems (e.g., ATS) are used to their fullest potential.</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>373121</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/26/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=373121&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>Atlanta</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>GA</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Account Director- Digital Strategy</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>Requirements: * BS/BA or equivalent experience required * 5+ years experience in Advertising/Marketing/PR client service * Must have experience developing and presenting custom digital solutions within a digital marketing, PR, and/or advertising agency environment * A demonstrated passion for search, social and mobile solutions and knowledge of how to leverage each to achieve marketing goals * Superior client service and demonstrated ability to grow internal and external client relationships * An understanding of the impact of social media across all digital marketing channels (and the ability to discuss the ROI of social media campaigns) * Deep understanding of the direction the digital landscape is going and a passion for all things digital * Demonstrated passion for technology and its use in driving revenue, client satisfaction and efficiency. * Flexibility to accommodate change and thrive amid ambiguity. * Exceptional communication skills (both written and verbal) and openness to providing feedback to help iterate the business. * Success in presenting strategic solutions and POVs that demonstrate thought leadership, and engage across social media * The ability to translate clients&#x2019; goals and objectives into actionable &amp; measurable digital marketing programs * Knowledge and understanding of social media platforms and their respective participants (Facebook, LinkedIn, YouTube, Twitter, etc.) and how they can be deployed in different scenarios * Should have strong understanding of interactive strategy, design, production and project management as well as tactics to leverage social media * Proven ability to solution sell and track record for closing digital business * Strong interpersonal, customer service, presentation, organizational and problem-solving skills * Strong self-discipline and time management skills. * Proven ability to understand customer needs and translate needs into solutions * Ability to balance revenue, client satisfaction and operational responsibilities while meeting deadlines * Strong knowledge of Excel, PowerPoint and other MS Office tools. * Strong quantitative and analytical skills. We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>Are you passionate about all aspects of digital advertising and providing clients with robust solutions and experiences that help them achieve their business objectives? Are you a driven and engaged professional who derives energy and creativity from working in a close-knit team environment? Big-picture thinking. Charismatic leadership. Long-term relationship building. That's what we expect from a Account Director- Digital Strategy at TMP. Here, you'll be part of a forward-thinking team charged with developing creative solutions that are transforming the way employers and job seekers connect. That means spearheading multi-pronged search, social and mobile marketing campaigns for a diverse suite of global organizations. Being the ambassador of our best-in-class technologies and digital capabilities to some of the most recognized companies in the world. And collaborating with people in every area and at every level of our organization on high-impact, enterprise-wide projects. All this in an environment that constantly challenges you to push beyond boundaries and enhance your expertise&#x2014;with the support of a global team of industry experts. Sound like a fit for your talent and passion? Read on. Responsibilities: * Monitor and manage all aspects of daily client performance * Act as the primary point of contact for assigned clients; escalate, track and solve client issues * Own the digital strategy for key client(s) * Support your region in achieving digital revenue goals by building strategic and creative digital marketing programs for clients, including Search, Social, Mobile and other Digital components * Introduce and evangelize our digital capabilities, emphasizing Search, Social and Mobile innovation * Lead agency thought leadership on social media channels * Develop in-depth knowledge of the industry and client business needs * Partner with Sales in pre-sales engagement work including developing proposals and campaign strategies that tie tightly with each client&#x2019;s media plans. * Drive established goals across relevant KPIs and balance business yield focused with client desired metrics. * Identify opportunities for performance improvement and upsell. * Working as a member of an account team to identify client needs and address them with strategic recommendation of TMP digital products and services * Maintain strong active relationships with key client stakeholders at both senior and mid-management levels; act as the primary point of contact for assigned clients * Comfortable and effective in complex project environments, and working with both long-range and short-term business objectives and management of multiple stakeholders * Interpreting and analyzing results data to improve client ROI * Delivering formal and informal presentations to clients as well as internal team members * Limited travel to sales / client offices or events may be required. To learn more about TMP Account Services and what we are working on- check out this link: https://www.tmp.com/client-services</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>380993</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/26/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=380993&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>Atlanta</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>GA</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Marketing Coordinator</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>Requirements: * Bachelor's degree in business administration or marketing * 1-3 years of experience in Marketing or Sales in a high tech company * Proficient with Microsoft office products including Outlook, Word, Excel and Powerpoint * Enjoys working in a fast paced environment * Strong communication skills * Should be creative, a self-starter, fast learner, detail oriented, multi-tasking and conscientious team player * Knowledge of Salesforce.com is a plus We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>Are you passionate about Marketing? Are you motivated by challenges? Do you want to know how it feels to be responsible for driving the success of a business? Then this is the job for you! As a Marketing Coordinator at TMP Worldwide, you will play an essential role in the project management and execution of our annual marketing activities for North America and Emerging Markets. We&#x2019;re seeking an organized, detail-oriented and highly adaptable Marketing Coordinator responsible for providing assistance and support with event execution, social monitoring, website content management, brand management, and more. Responsibilities: * Support the marketing team in implementing tactical events and programs, and provide project and administrative support * Assist in the execution of marketing events, such as trade shows and conferences * Preparation of PowerPoint presentations and Excel reporting as directed * Assist with managing the production of advertising, sales tools, marketing and promotional materials * Interface with internal customers (especially sales support and the sales team) * Coordinate web content updates, and assist with tracking website stats * Assist with the execution of marketing programs and promotions * Assist in other job functions within Sales and Marketing during month-end close activities * Develop product knowledge across all areas of TMP Worldwide software products and services</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>381894</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/26/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=381894&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>McLean</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>VA</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Copywriter</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>* B.A. degree from four-year college or university * Strong proofreading skill * Demonstrated creative ability; strong writing, verbal and presentation skills; * Must have attention to detail * Ability to work within strict deadlines * Excellent presentation skills We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>Please include writing samples or a link to your portfolio! COPYWRITER You will be part of an integrated creative department charged with leading our agency in innovation, creativity and execution. You can conceive, develop and manage an exceptional digital creative product. Thriving in a very fast paced, deadline driven environment. Creativity and accuracy. That&#x2019;s a Copywriter at TMP . You&#x2019;ll create copy for digital and traditional advertising, large scale web development, event promotion and much more. You&#x2019;ll be expected to work in digital, social and mobile environments as well as traditional print media. That means you&#x2019;ll need to be able to write on-brand and SEO-friendly web copy, as well as the billboards that lead people to the website. Working independently and with direction, you will fulfill requests large and small, continually focused on clearly and effectively communicating with your audience. From concept development to project execution, you must be a dependable resource of high quality work. Focused and detailed, the only match for your creativity and communication talents are your strong proofreading and organization skills. Responsibilities: * You will be well versed in content creation, social networking, search engine tools, keyword tracking, accessibility standards and digital media trends. * Define the needs and develop the creative strategy for clients, including listening, asking, hearing, prioritizing and translating client needs into strategic documents. * Ensure the creative product stays ahead of the competition and exceeds client expectations. * Develop effective copy for all advertising needs including but not limited to: traditional ad campaigns, websites, email campaigns, banner advertising, social media, presentations, creative rationales, Request For Proposals * Actively participate in client problem solving as part of integrated account team * Set the example and expectations for creative team work ethic, attitude and desire to be the best at what we do individually and as a team * Conduct and participate in new business pitches and client meetings; develop relationships and communication with internal departments and clients to proactively support their need * Perform ongoing research of print, online and multimedia capabilities * Continually stay abreast of the latest and greatest in the digital world including understanding usability, browser environment, search engine marketing, search engine algorithms and more * Other duties as required to succeed as a creative department</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>372822</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/25/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=372822&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>Coral Gables</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>FL</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Account Executive - Digital Advertising</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>* Bachelor&#x2019;s degree * 1-3 years digital or online advertising industry experience preferred * Knowledge and understanding of social media platforms and their respective participants (Facebook, LinkedIn, YouTube, Twitter, etc.) and how they can be deployed in different scenarios * Familiarity with various interactive mediums including: websites, banners, kiosks, Tablet PCs, etc. * Customer service experience specifically as it relates to the Human Resources or Advertising fields * Demonstrated experience uncovering business needs and building relationships with clients * Exceptional communication skills (both written and verbal) and openness to providing feedback to help iterate the business. * Strong interpersonal, customer service, presentation, organizational and problem-solving skills * Strong self-discipline and time management skills. * Ability to understand customer needs and translate needs into solutions * Ability to work collaboratively with a multi-disciplinary team * Detail oriented and Accuracy a must * Strong self-discipline and time management skills. * Strong knowledge of Excel, PowerPoint and other MS Office tools. * Experience managing clients on project scope and delivery. * Ability to handle many projects at one time and maintain calm under pressure. * Able to take direction and criticism. * Self &#x2013;motivated. We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>Are you passionate about all aspects of digital advertising and providing clients with robust solutions and experiences that help them achieve their business objectives? Are you a driven and engaged professional who derives energy and creativity from working in a close-knit team environment? It&#x2019;s a great time to join TMP &#x2013; we&#x2019;re seeking an Account Executive. We're looking for someone who truly understands and has a passion for innovation and delivering solutions for your clients. In this role, you will work closely with your assigned clients to identify their needs and/or challenges and recommend targeted solutions that incorporate appropriate TMP digital products and services. Someone who possesses project management orientation is essential as well as an ability to engender trust and confidence with your clients. Responsibilities: * Act as point of contact for assigned clients; escalate, track and solve client issues * Develop and maintain strong active relationships with key client stakeholders * Manages and oversees client&#x2019;s job posting requests in print and interactive media * Working as a member of an account team to identify client needs and address them with strategic recommendation of TMP digital products and services * Develop in-depth knowledge of the industry and client business needs * Identify opportunities for performance improvement and upsell. * Works as part of an interdisciplinary team of agency professionals including production, creative, media, finance and billing * Work with Account Directors, Business Development and proposal team to aid in answering inquiries from potential clients * Provide client reporting on an as-needed basis * Visit clients for meet and greet and/or presenting performance data and additional products and services--both formal and informal * Developing project estimates. * Developing project plans. * Ad placement, Insertion Orders (I.O.s) and contacting media * Assisting with creation of project scopes and proposals (deliverables, schedules, budgets, etc.) * Developing and maintaining critical issues documents. * Conducting project status meetings. * Preparing billing and forecast incomes ? * Working with Account Executives, Copywriters, Art Directors, Developers and Coordinators to fulfill client requests and expectations * Preparing all scope change documentation for Clients approval * Preparing functional specifications with project developers? * Providing Clients with all production schedules and critical milestones To learn more about TMP Account Services and what we are working on- check out this link: https://www.tmp.com/client-services</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>381430</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/25/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=381430&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>New York</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>NY</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Project Manager - ScrumMaster</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>Requirements * Bachelors Degree (ideally in Business or Computer Science) * 5+ years experience as a project manager in a software development environment, including 1 year in an agile team as scrum master. If you&#x2019;ve been through a waterfall-to-agile transition, all the better. Project management and/or Scrummaster certification desirable. * Significant experience project managing a distributed team across diverse cultures and time zones. * Understanding of web development and associated technologies. You don&#x2019;t need to have experience as a software developer, but you do need to know enough to follow technical discussions and bridge communications between product managers and developers. * Excellent interpersonal communications. Must have the ability to help product managers formulate/articulate a decision on the course of action. * Commitment to doing what it takes to meet project milestones * Quick learner, able to work independently with limited supervision. * Self motivated, proactive and dependable. * Team player &#x2013; positive, committed and selfless, willing to pitch in and help others when needed. * Organized, patient, able to works effectively under pressure. * Able to organize oneself and others. * Flexible to shifting priorities. We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>Overview: Innovative strategies. Proactive thinking. Comprehensive know-how. That's what we expect from a Project Manager at TMP. Here, you'll be part of a fiercely collaborative technology team charged with creating digital solutions that are transforming the way employers and job seekers connect. That means contributing to high-traffic websites for a broad range of high-profile companies. Developing next-generation applications and products for some of the most recognized brands in the world. And actively supporting our diverse suite of best-in-class technologies. All this in an environment that constantly challenges you to push beyond boundaries and enhance your expertise&#x2014;with the support of a global team of industry experts. Sound like a fit for your talent and passion? Read on. As a Project Manager in TMP&#x2019;s Product Engineering group, you will oversee software development projects from initiation through release, delivering new and enhanced products to our client base. The Project Manager must be able to harness a distributed and multi-functional team covering digital development in all its forms (design, IXD, content, UI development, engineering and quality assurance) and have the ability to facilitate dialog between developers and product managers. This is a fast-paced environment with lots to learn. Responsibilities * Serve as Scrummaster for software/ web development of new or enhanced products using agile methodology * Collaborate with distributed teams of product managers, developers, and QA testers to resource, define, and schedule activities required to develop and launch new software. Team members are onshore and offshore. * Define and enforce best practices. * Coordinate all production releases including weekly maintenance releases * Provide management-level reporting on project status, risks and mitigation strategies.</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>371880</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/25/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=371880&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>Chicago</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>IL</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Account Executive - Digital Advertising</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>Requirements &amp; Skills: * Bachelor&#x2019;s degree * 1-3 years digital or online advertising industry experience preferred * Knowledge and understanding of social media platforms and their respective participants (Facebook, LinkedIn, YouTube, Twitter, etc.) and how they can be deployed in different scenarios * Familiarity with various interactive mediums including: websites, banners, kiosks, Tablet PCs, etc. * Customer service experience specifically as it relates to the Human Resources or Advertising fields * Demonstrated experience uncovering business needs and building relationships with clients * Exceptional communication skills (both written and verbal) and openness to providing feedback to help iterate the business. * Strong interpersonal, customer service, presentation, organizational and problem-solving skills * Strong self-discipline and time management skills. * Ability to understand customer needs and translate needs into solutions * Ability to work collaboratively with a multi-disciplinary team * Detail oriented and Accuracy a must * Strong self-discipline and time management skills. * Strong knowledge of Excel, PowerPoint and other MS Office tools. * Experience managing clients on project scope and delivery. * Ability to handle many projects at one time and maintain calm under pressure. * Able to take direction and criticism. We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>Are you passionate about all aspects of digital advertising and providing clients with robust solutions and experiences that help them achieve their business objectives? Are you a driven and engaged professional who derives energy and creativity from working in a close-knit team environment? It&#x2019;s a great time to join TMP &#x2013; we&#x2019;re seeking an Account Executive. We're looking for someone who truly understands and has a passion for innovation and delivering solutions for your clients. In this role, you will work closely with your assigned clients to identify their needs and/or challenges and recommend targeted solutions that incorporate appropriate TMP digital products and services. Someone who possesses project management orientation is essential as well as an ability to engender trust and confidence with your clients. Responsibilities: * Act as point of contact for assigned clients; escalate, track and solve client issues * Develop and maintain strong active relationships with key client stakeholders * Manages and oversees client&#x2019;s job posting requests in print and interactive media * Working as a member of an account team to identify client needs and address them with strategic recommendation of TMP digital products and services * Develop in-depth knowledge of the industry and client business needs * Identify opportunities for performance improvement and upsell. * Works as part of an interdisciplinary team of agency professionals including production, creative, media, finance and billing * Work with Account Directors, Business Development and proposal team to aid in answering inquiries from potential clients * Provide client reporting on an as-needed basis * Visit clients for meet and greet and/or presenting performance data and additional products and services--both formal and informal * Developing project estimates. * Developing project plans. * Ad placement, Insertion Orders (I.O.s) and contacting media * Assisting with creation of project scopes and proposals (deliverables, schedules, budgets, etc.) * Developing and maintaining critical issues documents. * Conducting project status meetings. * Working with Creative Teams to fulfill client requests and expectations * Preparing all scope change documentation for Clients approval</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>361730</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/25/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=361730&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>Chicago</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>IL</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Digital Media Planner/Strategist</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>* 3-5 years (combined) experience with online media planning and web/media analytics and reporting * Critical thinker who can present complex concepts, media recommendations and data results in a clear and effective manner * Ability to work with MS Office product suite including exceptional PowerPoint and Excel skills, Access a plus * The ability to manage multiple priorities in an ever-changing environment and meet tight deadlines * Be a self-starter who can work independently as well as part of a team * Strong written and verbal communication, organization, negotiation and troubleshooting skills * Availability to travel up to 10% of the time * Recruitment advertising experience * Google Analytics certification or equivalent experience * Knowledge of social metrics (i.e., Facebook &amp; YouTube insights) * Experience using comScore and 3rd party ad serving technology (i.e., DoubleClick) We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>The Digital Media Planner bridges the gap between data and meaning. Part detective, part scientist, part storyteller, the role has elements of media planning, performance analysis and client service. The ideal candidate can research and negotiate media, clearly articulate how the media elements work and why we recommend them, and then objectively evaluate and synthesize the results for clients. Responsibilities: * Work directly with clients and account teams to understand overall objectives and how they relate to a client&#x2019;s media/web/social/mobile presence * Use this client knowledge to build integrated media plans that achieve client goals * Analyze the results and make optimization recommendations while the media is live and use empirical data to improve results for the next buying cycle * Write customized analysis including online media, search engine campaigns, social metrics, mobile metrics, and web analytics that highlight campaign strengths and weaknesses and provide actionable insights on campaign performance * Tell the full media story of the campaign lifecycle from inception through optimization to results, and do so in a client-facing, consultative manner * Lead support team consisting of Media Planners and Analysts to support client&#x2019;s media/web/social/mobile objectives * Evaluate new advertising opportunities * Work closely with media to negotiate packages to offer the best value to clients * Manage multiple projects and clients at any given time * Present complex concepts and metrics in a user-friendly way To learn more about the TMP Chicago office and what we are working on- check out these links: https://www.tmp.com/tmp-office-spotlight-chicago</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>368809</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/25/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=368809&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>New York</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>NY</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Paid Spring Internship - Product Management</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>Requirements: * Currently enrolled in a degree-seeking program at an accredited college or university entering your Junior or Senior year, ideally in a Computer Science, Business, or Marketing program with a desire to work in product management * Proficiency with basic computer programs (Mac platform) * 2-3 years of course work or experience * &#xad;&#xad;&#xad;&#xad;Ability to work a maximum of 20 hours per week * Positive, proactive &amp; energetic attitude, strong work ethic &amp; highly dependable * Exceptional communication skills (both written and verbal) and openness to providing feedback to help iterate the business. * Strong interpersonal, customer service, presentation, organizational and problem-solving skills * Strong self-discipline and time management skills. * Able to take direction * Self &#x2013;motivated. We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>Are you looking for a career in &#xad;&#xad;&#xad;&#xad;Technology &#x2013; Product Management? Are you interested in seeing what a full service digital advertising agency work experience would be like? If so TMP Worldwide Advertising &amp; Communications, LLC is the place for you! We are looking for interns in the &#xad;&#xad;&#xad;&#xad;Product Management field to work closely with our Product Development department. This highly selective program offers participants an opportunity to explore the fundamental elements of the digital advertising industry within a leading digital advertising agency environment. We aim to cultivate our interns&#x2019; skill set across the business spectrum through hands-on learning, rotations, interaction with senior management, presentations and work related projects. Program Structure: * Experiential learning environment * Learning objectives are coordinated with projects and supervisory feedback to enhance your understanding of business responsibilities * E-Learning online instruction is combined with hands-on experiences to augment learning * Interaction with our experts to gain greater insight into the multitude of career opportunities * Increased understanding of the importance of coordination between functional areas to deliver the best business results * Completion of a project presented to executives and other senior management to assist in understanding real world applications</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>336003</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/25/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=336003&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>Glendale</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>CA</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Account Executive - Digital Advertising</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>* Bachelor&#x2019;s degree * 1-3 years digital or online advertising industry experience preferred * Knowledge and understanding of social media platforms and their respective participants (Facebook, LinkedIn, YouTube, Twitter, etc.) and how they can be deployed in different scenarios * Familiarity with various interactive mediums including: websites, banners, kiosks, Tablet PCs, etc. * Customer service experience specifically as it relates to the Human Resources or Advertising fields * Demonstrated experience uncovering business needs and building relationships with clients * Exceptional communication skills (both written and verbal) and openness to providing feedback to help iterate the business. * Strong interpersonal, customer service, presentation, organizational and problem-solving skills * Strong self-discipline and time management skills. * Ability to understand customer needs and translate needs into solutions * Ability to work collaboratively with a multi-disciplinary team * Detail oriented and Accuracy a must * Strong self-discipline and time management skills. * Strong knowledge of Excel, PowerPoint and other MS Office tools. * Experience managing clients on project scope and delivery. * Ability to handle many projects at one time and maintain calm under pressure. * Able to take direction and criticism. * Self &#x2013;motivated. We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>Are you passionate about all aspects of digital advertising and providing clients with robust solutions and experiences that help them achieve their business objectives? Are you a driven and engaged professional who derives energy and creativity from working in a close-knit team environment? It&#x2019;s a great time to join TMP &#x2013; we&#x2019;re seeking an Advertising Account Executive. We're looking for someone who truly understands and has a passion for innovation and delivering solutions for your clients. In this role, you will work closely with your assigned clients to identify their needs and/or challenges and recommend targeted solutions that incorporate appropriate TMP digital products and services. Someone who possesses project management orientation is essential as well as an ability to engender trust and confidence with your clients. Responsibilities: * Act as point of contact for assigned clients; escalate, track and solve client issues * Develop and maintain strong active relationships with key client stakeholders * Manages and oversees client&#x2019;s job posting requests in print and interactive media * Working as a member of an account team to identify client needs and address them with strategic recommendation of TMP digital products and services * Develop in-depth knowledge of the industry and client business needs * Identify opportunities for performance improvement and upsell. * Works as part of an interdisciplinary team of agency professionals including production, creative, media, finance and billing * Work with Account Directors, Business Development and proposal team to aid in answering inquiries from potential clients * Provide client reporting on an as-needed basis * Developing project estimates. * Developing project plans. * Ad placement, Insertion Orders (I.O.s) and contacting media * Assisting with creation of project scopes and proposals (deliverables, schedules, budgets, etc.) * Developing and maintaining critical issues documents. * Conducting project status meetings. * Preparing all scope change documentation for Clients approval * Providing Clients with all production schedules and critical milestones To learn more about TMP Account Services and what we are working on- check out this link: http://www.jobsattmp.com/livestrategy</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>336760</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=336760&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>Milwaukee</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>WI</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Financial Planning and Analysis (FP&amp;A) Manager</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>* BS in Finance, Accounting, or related field; an MBA is preferred * 8-10 years of success in development and execution of financial planning processes, financial analyses, management reporting and business metrics * 3-5 years of FP&amp;A management experience * Strong data analysis skills; financial/business modeling experience a plus * High proficiency in MS Office, particularly with Excel, Access and PowerPoint * Functional knowledge of financial reporting systems and methodologies such as Essbase and Oracle * Effective oral and written communication skills with a strong ability to efficiently communicate financial results to both financially and non-financially oriented persons * Initiative; originate productive actions without specific instructions; generate new ideas, processes and approaches to meet business needs * Flexibility; someone who is adaptive to frequent changes in priorities, organization and strategy; flexible to deadlines with short lead times * Ability to balance multiple, diverse priorities and produce deliverables of high quality * Consummate professionalism and ability to communicate with all levels of an organization We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>We are looking for a Financial Planning and Analysis (FP&amp;A) Manager to oversee budgeting, forecasting and various analytical processes across the company. You will manage a small team of analysts while closely collaborating with company executives to drive accountability and visibility in the organization. The FP&amp;A Manager is a key member of the Financial Planning and Analysis team responsible for all corporate departments. The Manager will drive and coordinate all key financial planning processes (Budget/Forecast/Strategic Planning) and maintain financial stability by establishing financial frameworks, monitoring and improving financial performance, preparing and analyzing financial reports, and managing the corporate team. Location: Office moving to NW Suburbs in near future Responsibilities: * Facilitate the annual P&amp;L budgeting process and subsequent monthly/quarterly forecasts * Perform periodic variance analysis of budgeted, forecasted and actual financial performance, clearly interpreting and documenting variance drivers * Author periodic written management reports summarizing P&amp;L performance and variance analysis results * Support all business unit managers in periodic financial and operational performance reviews, helping to draft presentations that clearly articulate the &#x201c;story&#x201d; implied by the analytical findings/insights * Assist in identifying and implementing financial and operationally relevant Key Performance Indicators across and within respective business units * Proactively develop the business unit managers&#x2019; proficiency in interpreting and acting on financial/quantitative metrics to improve organizational performance; assist them, in conjunction with the Operations team, to develop and measure actionable plans * Proactively analyze the financial stability (profitability) of individual accounts (clients), identify drivers and make recommendations * Support business unit managers in developing financial information for RFP &amp; Pricing submissions * Assist in establishing and maintaining various reusable reporting templates * Take an active role in further developing TMP&#x2019;s Financial Reporting and Analysis policies and procedures, producing high quality documentation as needed * Execute ad-hoc financial/quantitative analysis and various reporting requests in support of business unit and corporate managers * Maintain a working knowledge of current principles and methodologies in financial reporting; profit planning, cost accounting and profitability analysis best-practices as they apply to service organizations</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>337149</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=337149&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>Milwaukee</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>WI</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Financial Analyst - Milwaukee</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>* BS in Finance, Accounting, or related field; an MBA is preferred * One to Three years of finance experience, preferably in a services organization * Strong data analysis skills; financial/business modeling experience a plus * High proficiency in MS Office, particularly with Excel, Access and PowerPoint * Functional knowledge of financial reporting systems and methodologies such as Essbase and Oracle * Effective oral and written communication skills with a strong ability to efficiently communicate financial results to both financially and non-financially oriented persons * Initiative; originate productive actions without specific instructions; generate new ideas, processes and approaches to meet business needs * Flexibility; someone who is adaptive to frequent changes in priorities, organization and strategy; flexible to deadlines with short lead times * Ability to balance multiple, diverse priorities and produce deliverables of high quality * Consummate professionalism and ability to communicate with all levels of an organization We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>As a Financial Analyst you will be primarily involved with illuminating business performance implied by financial/quantitative metrics and ad-hoc data analysis, helping establish new, actionable, operating metrics and reports, and iii. evaluating and analyzing sales data as it relates to the various compensation plans. These core objectives will be met by executing various financial/data analysis and reporting activities at both the business unit and corporate levels. Location: Office moving to NW Suburbs in near future Responsibilities: * Facilitate the annual P&amp;L budgeting process and subsequent monthly/quarterly forecasts * Perform periodic variance analysis of budgeted, forecasted and actual financial performance, clearly interpreting and documenting variance drivers * Author periodic written management reports summarizing P&amp;L performance and variance analysis results * Support all business unit managers in periodic financial and operational performance reviews, helping to draft presentations that clearly articulate the &#x201c;story&#x201d; implied by the analytical findings/insights * Assist in identifying and implementing financial and operationally relevant Key Performance Indicators across and within respective business units * Proactively develop the business unit managers&#x2019; proficiency in interpreting and acting on financial/quantitative metrics to improve organizational performance; assist them, in conjunction with the Operations team, to develop and measure actionable plans * Proactively analyze the financial stability (profitability) of individual accounts (clients), identify drivers and make recommendations * Take an active role in further developing TMP&#x2019;s Financial Reporting and Analysis policies and procedures, producing high quality documentation as needed * Execute ad-hoc financial/quantitative analysis and various reporting requests in support of business unit and corporate managers * Maintain a working knowledge of current principles and methodologies in financial reporting; profit planning, cost accounting and profitability analysis best-practices as they apply to service organizations * Administer company compensation programs and assure employees are paid accurately based on those plans * Assist the HR and payroll departments with confidential compensation related tasks</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>348598</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=348598&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>Chicago</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>IL</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Metrics Analyst &#x2013; Media &amp; Analytics</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>**An Excel and Access proficiency test will be required as part of the interview process.** * Expert level proficiency in MS Excel &amp; Access * 1+ years of digital advertising experience with strong knowledge of online advertising , search marketing, social metrics and digital media * Ability to present complex concepts and data analyses results in a clear and effective manner * Strong analytical, critical thinking, troubleshooting and problem-solving skills * Ability to manage multiple priorities in an fast-paced, ever changing environment * Must be a self-starter with the ability to work independently as well as collaborate with team members * Extremely detail-oriented and organized with a high level of commitment and follow through * Experience with 3rd party ad servers such as Doubleclick or MediaMind * Excellent verbal and written communication skills * Google Analytics certification a plus We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>It&#x2019;s a great time to join TMP &#x2013; we&#x2019;re seeking a Metrics Analyst in our Chicago office. In this unique role you will be responsible for extracting, transforming and aggregating data from various systems to meet the needs of the Metrics Analysts. In this role you will work with data from third-party ad servers, web analytics platforms, social media platforms, search engines, proprietary data warehouses and various other sources. We are seeking an Excel geek, if V lookups, array formulas, named ranges, nested functions, web queries and pivot tables are part of your vocabulary then this position may be for you. Essential Functions: * Will generate and compile accurate, in-depth monthly reports from various sources including but not limited to Doubleclick, Google Analytics, social sites and TMP proprietary sites * Define data output formats and export data from several internal and external sources * Clean or augment data as needed * Aggregate data based on defined criteria * Create template or custom reports based on client needs * Ensuring the completeness and accuracy of all data * Complete Ad-hoc reports or tasks as required * Identify reporting and data discrepancies as part of the support process for quality assurance (QA) * Leads QA and troubleshooting for creative, ad tags and floodlight tag issues * Communicate and address any data anomalies, data gaps, issues and provide information to appropriate stakeholders * Proof all work and check for anomalies or unexpected patterns * Load completed data into report and provide annotations where needed **An Excel and Access proficiency test will be required as part of the interview process.** To learn more about the TMP Chicago office and what we are working on- check out these links: https://www.tmp.com/tmp-office-spotlight-chicago</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>348692</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=348692&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>Milwaukee</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>WI</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>T&amp;E Accountant &#x2013; Intern</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>Qualifications: * Currently enrolled in a degree-seeking program at an accredited college or university, ideally in Accounting or Finance * Detail-oriented with strong analytical and interpersonal skills * Positive, proactive &amp; energetic attitude, strong work ethic &amp; highly dependable * Exceptional communication skills (both written and verbal) * Strong self-discipline and time management skills. * Able to take direction and criticism. * Self &#x2013;motivated. We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>This position will include several responsibilities, including, but not limited to the following: Expense Report Preparation: This individual is responsible to coordinate with Company employees to ensure the timely and accurate preparation of their Travel &amp; Expense reports. * Coordinating with Company employees to obtain necessary T&amp;E support documents * Prepare T&amp;E reports in accordance with Company policy * Review T&amp;E transactions to ensure policy compliance * Research and resolve T&amp;E issues within Oracle * Manage workflow to ensure the timely Managerial review and approval of T&amp;E reports and submission to payroll Accounting Verification: This individual is responsible to ensure that the T&amp;E activity is properly coded to the General Ledger accounts when the reports are submitted. Assist with the research and resolution of any T&amp;E related accounting issues escalated by the Accounting or Payroll teams. T&amp;E Audit Assistance: This individual is responsible to provide assistance to the T&amp;E Audit function. This will entail coordinate responses from the Company&#x2019;s travelers and ensuring that the proper supporting documents are in accordance with documentation standards.</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>355787</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=355787&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>New York</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>NY</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Digital Strategist</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>Requirements: * Bachelor&#x2019;s degree * Must have 3-5 years of experience developing and presenting custom digital solutions within a digital marketing, PR, and/or advertising agency environment * A demonstrated passion for search, social and mobile solutions and knowledge of how to leverage each to achieve marketing goals * Demonstrated experience building and executing digital/social media campaigns across social media platforms and emerging social networks/technologies * Strong knowledge of user-generated content, web video, and viral marketing on the web. * An understanding of web/campaign analytics, including usage of various analytics tools and software programs * An understanding of the impact of social media across all digital marketing channels (and the ability to discuss the ROI of social media campaigns) * Strong understanding of digital strategy, design, production and project management as well as tactics to leverage social media * Deep understanding of the direction the digital landscape is going and a passion for all things digital * The ability to translate clients&#x2019; goals and objectives into actionable and measurable digital marketing programs * Superior client service and demonstrated ability to grow internal and external client relationships * Proven ability to solution sell and track record for closing digital business * Superior written and verbal communication, interpersonal, organizational, public speaking, and customer service skills * Knowledge of digital and traditional media We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>Big-picture thinking. Charismatic leadership. Long-term relationship building. That's what we expect from a Digital Strategist at TMP. Here, you'll be part of a forward-thinking team charged with developing creative solutions that are transforming the way employers and job seekers connect. That means spearheading multi-pronged search, social and mobile marketing campaigns for a diverse suite of global organizations. Being the ambassador of our best-in-class technologies and digital capabilities to some of the most recognized companies in the world. And collaborating with people in every area and at every level of our organization on high-impact, enterprise-wide projects. All this in an environment that constantly challenges you to push beyond boundaries and enhance your expertise&#x2014;with the support of a global team of industry experts. Sound like a fit for your talent and passion? Read on. To learn more about TMP Digital Strategy and what we are working on- check out this link: https://www.tmp.com/digital-strategist-inside-scoop-what-to-read-before-you-apply Responsibilities: * Own the digital strategy for key client(s) * Support your region in achieving digital revenue goals by building strategic and creative digital marketing programs for clients, including Search, Social, Mobile and other Digital components * Work with the account and creative teams to guide the development and presentation of more complex, innovative and targeted digital solutions * Introduce and evangelize our digital capabilities, emphasizing Search, Social and Mobile innovation * Lead agency thought leadership on social media channels * Support Business Development staff with creative and strategic outlines as part of the RFP or proposal process * Help secure business by educating prospective clients on TMP&#x2019;s comprehensive digital offering * Stay up-to-date with Search, Social, and Mobile trends and innovations * Analyze metrics data to make recommendations that will increase client ROI * Deliver formal and informal presentations to help win and educate clients, prospects and internal teams * Develop written documentation such as proposals, presentations and client case studies</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>355788</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=355788&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>Waltham</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>MA</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Digital Strategist</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>Requirements: * Bachelor&#x2019;s degree * Must have 3-5 years of experience developing and presenting custom digital solutions within a digital marketing, PR, and/or advertising agency environment * A demonstrated passion for search, social and mobile solutions and knowledge of how to leverage each to achieve marketing goals * Demonstrated experience building and executing digital/social media campaigns across social media platforms and emerging social networks/technologies * Strong knowledge of user-generated content, web video, and viral marketing on the web. * An understanding of web/campaign analytics, including usage of various analytics tools and software programs * An understanding of the impact of social media across all digital marketing channels (and the ability to discuss the ROI of social media campaigns) * Strong understanding of digital strategy, design, production and project management as well as tactics to leverage social media * Deep understanding of the direction the digital landscape is going and a passion for all things digital * The ability to translate clients&#x2019; goals and objectives into actionable and measurable digital marketing programs * Superior client service and demonstrated ability to grow internal and external client relationships * Proven ability to solution sell and track record for closing digital business * Superior written and verbal communication, interpersonal, organizational, public speaking, and customer service skills * Knowledge of digital and traditional media We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>Big-picture thinking. Charismatic leadership. Long-term relationship building. That's what we expect from a Digital Strategist at TMP. Here, you'll be part of a forward-thinking team charged with developing creative solutions that are transforming the way employers and job seekers connect. That means spearheading multi-pronged search, social and mobile marketing campaigns for a diverse suite of global organizations. Being the ambassador of our best-in-class technologies and digital capabilities to some of the most recognized companies in the world. And collaborating with people in every area and at every level of our organization on high-impact, enterprise-wide projects. All this in an environment that constantly challenges you to push beyond boundaries and enhance your expertise&#x2014;with the support of a global team of industry experts. Sound like a fit for your talent and passion? Read on. To learn more about TMP Digital Strategy and what we are working on- check out this link: https://www.tmp.com/digital-strategist-inside-scoop-what-to-read-before-you-apply Responsibilities: * Own the digital strategy for key client(s) * Support your region in achieving digital revenue goals by building strategic and creative digital marketing programs for clients, including Search, Social, Mobile and other Digital components * Work with the account and creative teams to guide the development and presentation of more complex, innovative and targeted digital solutions * Introduce and evangelize our digital capabilities, emphasizing Search, Social and Mobile innovation * Lead agency thought leadership on social media channels * Support Business Development staff with creative and strategic outlines as part of the RFP or proposal process * Help secure business by educating prospective clients on TMP&#x2019;s comprehensive digital offering * Stay up-to-date with Search, Social, and Mobile trends and innovations * Analyze metrics data to make recommendations that will increase client ROI * Deliver formal and informal presentations to help win and educate clients, prospects and internal teams * Develop written documentation such as proposals, presentations and client case studies</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>357493</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=357493&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY>Singapore</JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>Singapore</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Account Executive - Digital Advertising</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>Requirements: * Bachelor&#x2019;s degree * 1-3 years digital or online advertising industry experience preferred * Knowledge and understanding of social media platforms and their respective participants (Facebook, LinkedIn, YouTube, Twitter, etc.) and how they can be deployed in different scenarios * Familiarity with various interactive mediums including: websites, banners, kiosks, Tablet PCs, etc. * Customer service experience specifically as it relates to the Human Resources or Advertising fields * Demonstrated experience uncovering business needs and building relationships with clients * Exceptional communication skills (both written and verbal) and openness to providing feedback to help iterate the business. * Strong interpersonal, customer service, presentation, organizational and problem-solving skills * Strong self-discipline and time management skills. * Ability to understand customer needs and translate needs into solutions * Ability to work collaboratively with a multi-disciplinary team * Detail oriented and Accuracy a must * Strong self-discipline and time management skills. * Strong knowledge of Excel, PowerPoint and other MS Office tools. * Experience managing clients on project scope and delivery. * Ability to handle many projects at one time and maintain calm under pressure. * Able to take direction and criticism. * Self &#x2013;motivated. We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>Are you passionate about all aspects of digital advertising and providing clients with robust solutions and experiences that help them achieve their business objectives? Are you a driven and engaged professional who derives energy and creativity from working in a close-knit team environment? It&#x2019;s a great time to join TMP &#x2013; we&#x2019;re seeking an Account Executive. We're looking for someone who truly understands and has a passion for innovation and delivering solutions for your clients. In this role, you will work closely with your assigned clients to identify their needs and/or challenges and recommend targeted solutions that incorporate appropriate TMP digital products and services. Someone who possesses project management orientation is essential as well as an ability to engender trust and confidence with your clients. Responsibilities: * Act as point of contact for assigned clients; escalate, track and solve client issues * Develop and maintain strong active relationships with key client stakeholders * Manages and oversees client&#x2019;s job posting requests in print and interactive media * Working as a member of an account team to identify client needs and address them with strategic recommendation of TMP digital products and services * Develop in-depth knowledge of the industry and client business needs * Identify opportunities for performance improvement and upsell. * Works as part of an interdisciplinary team of agency professionals including production, creative, media, finance and billing * Work with Account Directors, Business Development and proposal team to aid in answering inquiries from potential clients * Provide client reporting on an as-needed basis * Visit clients for meet and greet and/or presenting performance data and additional products and services--both formal and informal * Developing project estimates. * Developing project plans. * Ad placement, Insertion Orders (I.O.s) and contacting media * Assisting with creation of project scopes and proposals (deliverables, schedules, budgets, etc.) * Developing and maintaining critical issues documents. * Conducting project status meetings. * Preparing billing and forecast incomes * Working with Account Executives, Copywriters, Art Directors, Developers and Coordinators to fulfill client requests and expectations * Preparing all scope change documentation for Clients approval * Preparing functional specifications with project developers * Providing Clients with all production schedules and critical milestones To learn more about TMP Account Services and what we are working on- check out this link: https://www.tmp.com/client-services</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>358909</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=358909&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>Glendale</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>CA</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Account Director - Digital Strategy - Glendale, CA</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>Requirements: * BS/BA or equivalent experience required * 5+ years experience in Advertising/Marketing/PR client service * Must have experience developing and presenting custom digital solutions within a digital marketing, PR, and/or advertising agency environment * A demonstrated passion for search, social and mobile solutions and knowledge of how to leverage each to achieve marketing goals * Superior client service and demonstrated ability to grow internal and external client relationships * An understanding of the impact of social media across all digital marketing channels (and the ability to discuss the ROI of social media campaigns) * Deep understanding of the direction the digital landscape is going and a passion for all things digital * Demonstrated passion for technology and its use in driving revenue, client satisfaction and efficiency. * Flexibility to accommodate change and thrive amid ambiguity. * Exceptional communication skills (both written and verbal) and openness to providing feedback to help iterate the business. * Success in presenting strategic solutions and POVs that demonstrate thought leadership, and engage across social media * The ability to translate clients&#x2019; goals and objectives into actionable &amp; measurable digital marketing programs * Knowledge and understanding of social media platforms and their respective participants (Facebook, LinkedIn, YouTube, Twitter, etc.) and how they can be deployed in different scenarios * Should have strong understanding of interactive strategy, design, production and project management as well as tactics to leverage social media * Proven ability to solution sell and track record for closing digital business * Strong interpersonal, customer service, presentation, organizational and problem-solving skills * Strong self-discipline and time management skills. * Proven ability to understand customer needs and translate needs into solutions * Ability to balance revenue, client satisfaction and operational responsibilities while meeting deadlines * Strong knowledge of Excel, PowerPoint and other MS Office tools. * Strong quantitative and analytical skills. We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>Are you passionate about all aspects of digital advertising and providing clients with robust solutions and experiences that help them achieve their business objectives? Are you a driven and engaged professional who derives energy and creativity from working in a close-knit team environment? Big-picture thinking. Charismatic leadership. Long-term relationship building. That's what we expect from a Account Director- Digital Strategy at TMP. Here, you'll be part of a forward-thinking team charged with developing creative solutions that are transforming the way employers and job seekers connect. That means spearheading multi-pronged search, social and mobile marketing campaigns for a diverse suite of global organizations. Being the ambassador of our best-in-class technologies and digital capabilities to some of the most recognized companies in the world. And collaborating with people in every area and at every level of our organization on high-impact, enterprise-wide projects. All this in an environment that constantly challenges you to push beyond boundaries and enhance your expertise&#x2014;with the support of a global team of industry experts. Sound like a fit for your talent and passion? Read on. Responsibilities: * Monitor and manage all aspects of daily client performance * Act as the primary point of contact for assigned clients; escalate, track and solve client issues * Own the digital strategy for key client(s) * Support your region in achieving digital revenue goals by building strategic and creative digital marketing programs for clients, including Search, Social, Mobile and other Digital components * Introduce and evangelize our digital capabilities, emphasizing Search, Social and Mobile innovation * Lead agency thought leadership on social media channels * Develop in-depth knowledge of the industry and client business needs * Partner with Sales in pre-sales engagement work including developing proposals and campaign strategies that tie tightly with each client&#x2019;s media plans. * Drive established goals across relevant KPIs and balance business yield focused with client desired metrics. * Identify opportunities for performance improvement and upsell. * Working as a member of an account team to identify client needs and address them with strategic recommendation of TMP digital products and services * Maintain strong active relationships with key client stakeholders at both senior and mid-management levels; act as the primary point of contact for assigned clients * Comfortable and effective in complex project environments, and working with both long-range and short-term business objectives and management of multiple stakeholders * Interpreting and analyzing results data to improve client ROI * Delivering formal and informal presentations to clients as well as internal team members * Limited travel to sales / client offices or events may be required. To learn more about TMP Account Services and what we are working on- check out this link: http://www.jobsattmp.com/live-digital</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>249946</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=249946&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>Chicago</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>IL</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Marketing Metrics- Digital Advertising - Intern</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>* Interest in marketing or advertising, with background in data or finance analysis * 1-2 years media digital experience a plus, but not required * Strong communication skills (written) and a positive attitude are a must. * A customer service focus and the ability to work as a team and independently are a necessity. * Able to successfully manage and prioritize multiple campaigns in a deadline-driven atmosphere. * Strong analytical skills: ability to gather, analyze, summarize, and present data. * Ability to manage multiple projects in a fast-paced environment and shift priorities quickly * Proficiency in Microsoft Excel, and Access * Familiar with tracking, analytics, and reporting including Doubleclick and Google Analytic We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>The TMP Worldwide Metrics Intern targets individuals looking for a future career in Advertising. This selective position offers participants an opportunity to explore the fundamental elements of the advertising industry within a leading advertising agency environment. We aim to cultivate skill set across the business spectrum through hands-on learning, rotations, interaction with multiple digital media properties and analysis of complex data sets. Responsibilities: * Generate and compile in-depth monthly reports from various sources include but not limited to Doubleclick, Google Analytics, social sites, and TMP proprietary sites. * Clean or augment data as needed. * Review basic KPI&#x2019;s such as CPA, CPH, and other specific ROI actions. * Communicate regularly on timeline for specific client performance reporting with data specialist or metrics analyst. To learn more about the TMP Chicago office and what we are working on- check out these links: https://www.tmp.com/tmp-office-spotlight-chicago</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>251017</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=251017&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY>Singapore</JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>Singapore</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Digital Media Planner</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>* Bachelor&#x2019;s degree * Must be fluent- read/write in Mandarin chinese and english. * Minimum 5 years account management and up-selling existing clients within a digital marketing, recruitment consulting and/or advertising agency environment * Proven ability to understand customer needs and translate needs into solutions * Experience in recruitment advertising, HR talent acquisition strategy and/or marketing preferre * Knowledge and understanding of social media platforms and their respective participants (Facebook, LinkedIn, YouTube, Twitter, etc.) and how they can be deployed in different scenarios * Should have strong understanding of interactive strategy, design, production and project management as well as tactics to leverage social media * Strong interpersonal, customer service, presentation, organizational and problem-solving skills * Proficiency with MS Office suite * The ability to travel as necessary We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>As a Digital Media Planner, you will be responsible for developing digital media strategies for a book of client business to help them achieve their hiring goals. If you have experience and a knack for Search engine marketing, social media strategy, mobile and other digital media this is a great opportunity for you. This role works closely with the account management team in developing successful integrated media campaigns for some of the largest employers in the world. Responsibilities: * Identifying and assessing client goals and objectives * Development of strategic and validated custom digital media plans based on historical ROI data and 3rd party Audit resources * Enabling client to gain a recruiting advantage in the market through the application of digital marketing techniques, tools and methodologies * Presenting &amp; selling plans to internal and external clients * Account Management on ad platforms for pay per click (ppc) media such as Google Adwords, Microsoft Adcenter, Facebook, and Job Aggregators * Manage SEM campaigns based on basic KPI&#x2019;s such as CTR, CPC, and specific ROI actions * Create, categorize and refine keyword lists to create a comprehensive campaign that drives qualified visitors to client sites. * Implement successful bidding strategies and effective keyword management using third party software using metrics data. * Continually monitor, revise, and conduct ad &amp; landing page tests * Analyze and assess the performance of campaigns and translate quantitative and qualitative data into recommendations and plans for revising the campaign strategy. * Communicate regularly on status, timeline, budget, deliverables, performance reporting, and competitive intelligence analysis with account service teams * Format and prepare periodic search reports for clients. Reports would be in the form of tables, graphs, summaries, and powerpoint slides * Present data on monthly &amp; quarterly calls to clients reviewing metrics &amp; optimizations</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>300268</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=300268&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>Milwaukee</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>WI</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Accountant - Milwaukee</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>* Bachelor's degree in accounting * 2-4 years of financial accounting experience * Experience with finance, accounting, budgeting and cost control procedures. * General understanding of the company income statements, balance sheets and cash flow requirement * Familiar with a variety of the field's concepts, practices, and procedures. * Individuals should have working knowledge of Microsoft Office * Ability to work over-time as required. * Relies on experience and judgment to plan and accomplish goals. * Performs a variety of complicated tasks with little or no guidance. * May lead and direct the work of others. * Offers assistance to other team members and provides support to the Accounting Supervisor when necessary. * A wide degree of creativity and latitude is expected. * Reports to the Accounting Manager. We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>It&#x2019;s a great time to join TMP &#x2013; we&#x2019;re seeking an Accountant. Under limited supervision performs all phases of the accounting process including month end and year end reports and statements, account analysis of assigned balance sheets and income statements, assists in the preparation of budgets management of daily cash flow, fixed asset management, consolidation of statements and the development of business metrics. Location: Office moving to NW Suburbs in near future Responsibilities: * Responsible for the monthly preparation of balance sheets, monthly internal profit and loss statements, and other financial reports. * Primary focus during the month-end includes, but is not limited to, recording and review of the detailed files received from the order entry sub-system, ensuring revenue recognition policies are followed, accuracy of orders/jobs created by field offices. * Responsibilities also include analyzing trends, costs, revenues, financial commitments, and obligations incurred to predict future revenues and expenses. * The individual will also be responsible for delivery of financial results, including Financial Statements, Balance Sheet Reports, Statement of Cash Flows, and any additional requests, to the local management. * Also responsible for preparation of complex balance sheet accounts as assigned including, but not limited too, the reconciliation of the company&#x2019;s estimated liability for sales. * Special projects as assigned</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>316582</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=316582&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY>Singapore</JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>Singapore</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Sr Account Director - Digital Advertising-Singapore</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>* BS/BA or equivalent experience required * 7+ years experience in Advertising/Marketing/PR client service * 5+ years digital or online advertising industry experience * Demonstrated passion for technology and its use in driving revenue, client satisfaction and efficiency. * Flexibility to accommodate change and thrive amid ambiguity. * Exceptional communication skills (both written and verbal) and openness to providing feedback to help iterate the business. * Demonstrated expertise in uncovering business needs and building relationships with senior level clients * A demonstrated passion for search, social and mobile solutions and knowledge of how to leverage each to achieve marketing goals * Success in presenting strategic solutions and POVs that demonstrate thought leadership, and engage across social media * The ability to translate clients&#x2019; goals and objectives into actionable &amp; measurable digital marketing programs * Knowledge and understanding of social media platforms and their respective participants (Facebook, LinkedIn, YouTube, Twitter, etc.) and how they can be deployed in different scenarios * Should have strong understanding of interactive strategy, design, production and project management as well as tactics to leverage social media * Deep understanding of the direction the digital landscape is going and a passion for all things digital * Proven ability to solution sell and track record for closing digital business * Strong interpersonal, customer service, presentation, organizational and problem-solving skills * Strong self-discipline and time management skills. * Proven ability to understand customer needs and translate needs into solutions * Ability to balance revenue, client satisfaction and operational responsibilities while meeting deadlines * Strong knowledge of Excel, PowerPoint and other MS Office tools. * Strong quantitative and analytical skills. We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>Are you passionate about all aspects of digital advertising and providing clients with robust solutions and experiences that help them achieve their business objectives? Are you a driven and engaged professional who derives energy and creativity from working in a close-knit team environment? As a Senior Account Director at TMP Singapore, you will play a significant role in growth and development of the TMP regional hub in Singapore and across the APAC region. This multi-faceted role embraces various aspects of the agency: account servicing, business development, strategy consulting, Employer Brand and Social Media. All this in the fast-paced environment of working in a regional role in Asia. We're looking for someone who is truly passionate about driving the agency strategy and growth through high value-add solutions for our clients and prospects. Flexibility, ability to handle pressure, work with senior HR and Talent leaders, ability to multi-task and willingness to learn in the ever-evolving Asia-Pacific market are all required for a successful candidate. Responsibilities: * Lead major accounts with regional APAC responsibility * Act as the primary point of contact for assigned clients; escalate, track and solve client issues * Develop and maintain strong active relationships with key client stakeholders * Monitor and manage all aspects of daily client performance * Manage a pipeline; responsible for weekly/monthly reporting * Drive organic growth within the assigned client portfolio * Develop in-depth knowledge of the industry and client business needs * Partner with Sales in pre-sales engagement work including developing proposals and campaign strategies that tie tightly with each client&#x2019;s goals and identified needs. * Drive established goals across relevant KPIs and balance business yield focused with client desired metrics. * Develop cooperation with global account team for best practices sharing and learning. * Identify opportunities for performance improvement and up-sell. * Working as a member of an account team to identify client needs and address them with strategic recommendation of TMP digital products and services * Maintain strong active relationships with key client stakeholders at both senior and mid-management levels; act as the primary point of contact for assigned clients * Comfortable and effective in complex project environments, and working with both long-range and short-term business objectives and management of multiple stakeholders * Interpreting and analyzing results data to improve client ROI * Delivering formal and informal presentations to clients as well as internal team members * Limited travel to sales / client offices or events may be required.</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>317238</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=317238&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>Milwaukee</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>WI</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Accounts Receivable Specialist - Milwaukee</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>Skills/Requirements: * High school diploma required, Associates Degree or higher preferred * Communicate effectively with internal and external customers, strong listening skills, ability to professionally handle difficult collection calls * Minimum of 2 years collection experience, including skip tracing and business to business collections * Familiarity with Excel, Word, Outlook, Oracle, and collections queuing systems * Comprehensive knowledge of collection strategies and techniques, providing excellent customer service with a professional demeanor in all situations * Demonstrates persistence: continuously strives to improve skills and achieve goals despite setbacks and obstacles * Strives to meet department goals * Effective organizational skills, ability to meet deadlines, able to work independently to set priorities * Ability to consistently meet and exceed department goals * Team player/leader * Approaches tasks with a positive attitude * Consistent month over month reduction in AR We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>It&#x2019;s a great time to join TMP, we&#x2019;re seeking an Account Receivable Specialist Responsibilities: * Takes ownership and accountability for all activity within portfolio. * Monitors customer account balances to prevent losses, communicates payment terms to clients, promptly notifies clients of outstanding balances and continuously follows up with client for payment * Ability to control delinquent balances by preparing, mailing, faxing, and/or emailing past due notices, strategic letters * Ability to assertively enforce payment terms * Comfortable establishing payment arrangements will clients * Familiar with skip tracing and contacting clients for payment * Coordinate monthly calls to the field offices for follow-up * Ability to provide detailed updates on collection activity and client information in collection system * Strive to hit aggressive goals set by management including managing sufficient call volume * Ability to make decisions without supervisor/manager&#x2019;s approval based on the dollar amount of the account/invoice being collected * Developing payment plans for accounts/clients * Able to offer settlements to clients</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>326938</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=326938&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>San Francisco</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>CA</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Account Executive - Digital Advertising</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>Requirements: * Bachelor&#x2019;s degree * 1-3 years digital or online advertising industry experience preferred * Knowledge and understanding of social media platforms and their respective participants (Facebook, LinkedIn, YouTube, Twitter, etc.) and how they can be deployed in different scenarios * Familiarity with various interactive mediums including: websites, banners, kiosks, Tablet PCs, etc. * Customer service experience specifically as it relates to the Human Resources or Advertising fields * Demonstrated experience uncovering business needs and building relationships with clients * Exceptional communication skills (both written and verbal) and openness to providing feedback to help iterate the business. * Strong interpersonal, customer service, presentation, organizational and problem-solving skills * Strong self-discipline and time management skills. * Ability to understand customer needs and translate needs into solutions * Ability to work collaboratively with a multi-disciplinary team * Detail oriented and Accuracy a must * Strong self-discipline and time management skills. * Strong knowledge of Excel, PowerPoint and other MS Office tools. * Ability to handle many projects at one time and maintain calm under pressure. * Able to take direction and criticism. * Self &#x2013;motivated. We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>Are you passionate about all aspects of digital advertising and providing clients with robust solutions and experiences that help them achieve their business objectives? Are you a driven and engaged professional who derives energy and creativity from working in a close-knit team environment? It&#x2019;s a great time to join TMP &#x2013; we&#x2019;re seeking an Account Executive. We're looking for someone who truly understands and has a passion for innovation and delivering solutions for your clients. In this role, you will work closely with your assigned clients to identify their needs and/or challenges and recommend targeted solutions that incorporate appropriate TMP digital products and services. Someone who possesses project management orientation is essential as well as an ability to engender trust and confidence with your clients. Responsibilities: * Act as point of contact for assigned clients; escalate, track and solve client issues * Develop and maintain strong active relationships with key client stakeholders * Manages and oversees client&#x2019;s job posting requests in print and interactive media * Working as a member of an account team to identify client needs and address them with strategic recommendation of TMP digital products and services * Develop in-depth knowledge of the industry and client business needs * Identify opportunities for performance improvement and upsell. * Works as part of an interdisciplinary team of agency professionals including production, creative, media, finance and billing * Work with Account Directors, Business Development and proposal team to aid in answering inquiries from potential clients * Provide client reporting on an as-needed basis * Visit clients for meet and greet and/or presenting performance data and additional products and services--both formal and informal * Ad placement, Insertion Orders (I.O.s) and contacting media * Assisting with creation of project scopes and proposals (deliverables, schedules, budgets, etc.) * Developing and maintaining critical issues documents. * Working with Account Executives, Copywriters, Art Directors, Developers and Coordinators to fulfill client requests and expectations * Preparing all scope change documentation for Clients approval * Providing Clients with all production schedules and critical milestones</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>327684</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=327684&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>Chicago</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>IL</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Intern - Copywriter - Spring</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>Requirements: * Currently enrolled in a degree-seeking program at an accredited college or university, ideally in an advertising/marketing/communications program with an emphasis in Copywriting * Proficiency with basic computer programs (Mac platform) * 1-2 years of course work or experience * Must submit samples of academic, professional or personal work which shows strong ability to write copy or design (digital design work preferred) * A demonstrated passion for social media and knowledge of how to leverage it * An understanding of the impact of social media across all digital marketing channels * Positive, proactive &amp; energetic attitude, strong work ethic &amp; highly dependable * Exceptional communication skills (both written and verbal) and openness to providing feedback to help iterate the business. * Strong interpersonal, customer service, presentation, organizational and problem-solving skills * Strong self-discipline and time management skills. * Able to take direction and criticism. * Self &#x2013;motivated. We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>The TMP Worldwide Internship Program targets top college and university students for a future career in Advertising. This highly selective program offers participants an opportunity to explore the fundamental elements of the advertising industry within a leading advertising agency environment. We aim to cultivate our interns&#x2019; skill set across the business spectrum through hands-on learning, rotations, interaction with senior management, presentations and work related projects. Program Structure: * Experiential learning environment * Learning objectives are coordinated with projects and supervisory feedback to enhance your understanding of business responsibilities * E-Learning online instruction is combined with hands-on experiences to augment learning * Interaction with our experts to gain greater insight into the multitude of career opportunities * Increased understanding of the importance of coordination between functional areas to deliver the best business results * Completion of a project presented to executives and other senior management to assist in understanding real world applications To learn more about the TMP Chicago office and what we are working on- check out these links: https://www.tmp.com/tmp-office-spotlight-chicago</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>334645</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=334645&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>Atlanta</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>GA</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Marketing Specialist- Digital Advertising-Metrics</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>* Bachelor&#x2019;s degree from accredited four year college or university * 1-3 years of internet advertising experience with strong knowledge of internet, PPC/search marketing and online advertising * Knowledge of basic html editing; familiarity with Flash, JavaScript code and/or 3rd party ad tags * Experience with 3rd party ad servers such as Doubleclick a definite plus * Excellent oral and written communication skills * Extremely detail-oriented and organized with a high level of commitment and follow through * Strong Microsoft office skills especially Microsoft Excel * Ability to manage multiple priorities in an fast-paced, ever changing environment We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>It&#x2019;s a great time to join TMP &#x2013; we&#x2019;re seeking a Marketing Specialist- Digital Advertising-Metrics in the Atlanta/Perimeter, GA area to join our Metrics Implementation team. Are you passionate about all aspects of digital advertising and providing clients with robust solutions and experiences that help them achieve their business objectives? Are you a driven and engaged professional who derives energy and creativity from working in a fast-paced, close-knit team environment? We're looking for someone who truly understands and has a passion for digital advertising, innovation and delivering solutions for your clients. In this role, you will be responsible for the implementation of multiple TMP clients&#x2019; online advertising campaigns. The Campaign Specialist takes ownership of the clients&#x2019; digital campaigns while providing support and making recommendations throughout the life of the campaign. Will also provide troubleshooting support and correct problems with campaigns. Essential Functions: * Implement and create ad tags for client&#x2019;s online media campaigns through the agency&#x2019;s third party ad server and work with websites to ensure that they are implemented and collecting data properly * Provide technical expertise to identify and resolve any issues with campaign tracking, DoubleClick tags, QA and/or reporting * Work closely with account teams &amp; analysts to ensure that campaigns are setup properly ensuring that client expectations and campaign goals are met * Troubleshoot technical issues, including malfunctioning tags, ad creative, click-through URLs, and landing pages, etc. * Work with creative team, account team and/or client to ensure creative standards are met * QA to ensure all launched campaigns continue to serve correctly for the scheduled time period * Maintain and build relationships with outside vendors, including but not limited to applicant tracking systems, 3rd party ad serving vendors and media vendors as well as TMP team members</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>370123</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=370123&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>Waltham</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>MA</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Account Executive - Digital Advertising</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>Requirements &amp; Skills: * Bachelor&#x2019;s degree * 1-3 years digital or online advertising industry experience preferred * Knowledge and understanding of social media platforms and their respective participants (Facebook, LinkedIn, YouTube, Twitter, etc.) and how they can be deployed in different scenarios * Familiarity with various interactive mediums including: websites, banners, kiosks, Tablet PCs, etc. * Customer service experience specifically as it relates to the Human Resources or Advertising fields * Demonstrated experience uncovering business needs and building relationships with clients * Exceptional communication skills (both written and verbal) and openness to providing feedback to help iterate the business. * Strong interpersonal, customer service, presentation, organizational and problem-solving skills * Strong self-discipline and time management skills. * Ability to understand customer needs and translate needs into solutions * Ability to work collaboratively with a multi-disciplinary team * Detail oriented and Accuracy a must * Strong self-discipline and time management skills. * Strong knowledge of Excel, PowerPoint and other MS Office tools. * Experience managing clients on project scope and delivery. * Ability to handle many projects at one time and maintain calm under pressure. * Able to take direction and criticism. * Self &#x2013;motivated. We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>Are you passionate about all aspects of digital advertising and providing clients with robust solutions and experiences that help them achieve their business objectives? Are you a driven and engaged professional who derives energy and creativity from working in a close-knit team environment? It&#x2019;s a great time to join TMP &#x2013; we&#x2019;re seeking an Advertising Account Executive. We're looking for someone who truly understands and has a passion for innovation and delivering solutions for your clients. In this role, you will work closely with your assigned clients to identify their needs and/or challenges and recommend targeted solutions that incorporate appropriate TMP digital products and services. Someone who possesses project management orientation is essential as well as an ability to engender trust and confidence with your clients. Responsibilities: * Act as point of contact for assigned clients; escalate, track and solve client issues * Develop and maintain strong active relationships with key client stakeholders * Manages and oversees client&#x2019;s job posting requests in print and interactive media * Working as a member of an account team to identify client needs and address them with strategic recommendation of TMP digital products and services * Develop in-depth knowledge of the industry and client business needs * Identify opportunities for performance improvement and upsell. * Works as part of an interdisciplinary team of agency professionals including production, creative, media, finance and billing * Work with Account Directors, Business Development and proposal team to aid in answering inquiries from potential clients * Provide client reporting on an as-needed basis * Developing project estimates. * Developing project plans. * Ad placement, Insertion Orders (I.O.s) and contacting media * Assisting with creation of project scopes and proposals (deliverables, schedules, budgets, etc.) * Developing and maintaining critical issues documents. * Conducting project status meetings. * Preparing all scope change documentation for Clients approval * Providing Clients with all production schedules and critical milestones To learn more about TMP Account Services and what we are working on- check out this link: https://www.tmp.com/client-services</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>370642</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=370642&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>McLean</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>VA</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Account Executive - Digital Advertising</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>Requirements &amp; Skills: * Bachelor&#x2019;s degree * 1-3 years digital or online advertising industry experience preferred * Knowledge and understanding of social media platforms and their respective participants (Facebook, LinkedIn, YouTube, Twitter, etc.) and how they can be deployed in different scenarios * Familiarity with various interactive mediums including: websites, banners, kiosks, Tablet PCs, etc. * Customer service experience specifically as it relates to the Human Resources or Advertising fields * Demonstrated experience uncovering business needs and building relationships with clients * Exceptional communication skills (both written and verbal) and openness to providing feedback to help iterate the business. * Strong interpersonal, customer service, presentation, organizational and problem-solving skills * Strong self-discipline and time management skills. * Ability to understand customer needs and translate needs into solutions * Ability to work collaboratively with a multi-disciplinary team * Detail oriented and Accuracy a must * Strong self-discipline and time management skills. * Strong knowledge of Excel, PowerPoint and other MS Office tools. * Experience managing clients on project scope and delivery. * Ability to handle many projects at one time and maintain calm under pressure. * Able to take direction and criticism. * Self &#x2013;motivated. We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>Are you passionate about all aspects of digital advertising and providing clients with robust solutions and experiences that help them achieve their business objectives? Are you a driven and engaged professional who derives energy and creativity from working in a close-knit team environment? It&#x2019;s a great time to join TMP &#x2013; we&#x2019;re seeking an Account Executive. We're looking for someone who truly understands and has a passion for innovation and delivering solutions for your clients. In this role, you will work closely with your assigned clients to identify their needs and/or challenges and recommend targeted solutions that incorporate appropriate TMP digital products and services. Someone who possesses project management orientation is essential as well as an ability to engender trust and confidence with your clients. Responsibilities: * Act as point of contact for assigned clients; escalate, track and solve client issues * Develop and maintain strong active relationships with key client stakeholders * Manages and oversees client&#x2019;s job posting requests in print and interactive media * Working as a member of an account team to identify client needs and address them with strategic recommendation of TMP digital products and services * Develop in-depth knowledge of the industry and client business needs * Identify opportunities for performance improvement and upsell. * Works as part of an interdisciplinary team of agency professionals including production, creative, media, finance and billing * Work with Account Directors, Business Development and proposal team to aid in answering inquiries from potential clients * Provide client reporting on an as-needed basis * Visit clients for meet and greet and/or presenting performance data and additional products and services--both formal and informal * Developing project estimates. * Developing project plans. * Ad placement, Insertion Orders (I.O.s) and contacting media * Assisting with creation of project scopes and proposals (deliverables, schedules, budgets, etc.) * Developing and maintaining critical issues documents. * Conducting project status meetings. * Working with Creative Teams to fulfill client requests and expectations * Preparing all scope change documentation for Clients approval</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>365363</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=365363&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>Atlanta</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>GA</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Product Support Specialist</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>Requirements: * Bachelor&#x2019;s Degree in Business or equivalent field/work experience * 1-3 years customer or technical support experience * Enjoys working on the phone to help clients with any product support issues or requests including but not limited to changes, trouble shooting, consultation * Ability to plan, organize, prioritize and independently solve problems seeking help when necessary * Strong project management skills * Ability to multi-task * Excellent communication (oral and written), interpersonal, organizational, and presentation skills * Knowledge of software development processes and concepts. Understanding of HTML, XML, API, JavaScript, CSS a plus * Proficient with Microsoft Office We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>TMP Worldwide needs experienced, energetic self-starters with excellent problem solving and customer service skills to deliver accurate and prompt technical and functional software support to our suite of online products. TMP&#x2019;s Product Support Specialists apply a consultative approach to diagnosing and resolving issues within a range of technical environments. As a Product Support Specialist at TMP Worldwide, you will be responsible for communicating with clients concerning their software needs and maintenance requests. The successful candidate should possess a high level of professionalism, technical knowledge, and requires the ability to work both independently and within a team in a fast based, creative and technical environment. Responsibilities: * Provide phone, email, and web based support for clients with software installations * Troubleshoot client and internal issues * Manage the escalation of issues, as required * Work closely with Digital Project Managers, Product Management, and Engineering teams in identifying, reporting, and resolving product issues and requests * Develop product expertise across all areas of the software products * Provide technical consultation to clients to determine solutions best suited for their needs * Develop and foster strategic relationships with clients * Set up and maintain users, user profiles, workflow rules, and application settings * Provide training to end users and conduct learning forums as needed * Manage and maintain accurate and thorough client support records * Conduct and/or assist with system enhancements, user application, and quality assurance testing</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>366773</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=366773&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>Chicago</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>IL</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Inbound Marketing Manager- Chicago</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>Requirements: * Bachelors Degree * Previous writing experience for brands * 2+ years of social media marketing experience including blogging, Facebook, Twitter, YouTube, and LinkedIn. * Experience managing a brand&#x2019;s social media presence from top to bottom * Has working knowledge of social analytics and key performance indicators * Experience with a content management system (Spreadfast, Adobe, hootsuite) * Can delegate tasks to team members that accomplish strategic initiatives * Strong working knowledge of a social media scheduling and distribution tool * Proficient in Power Point, Excel and other related applications * Superior communication and organizational skills We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>We&#x2019;re a team of 14 in Chicago who think up, build, and deliver the best recruiting content and social media to 50+ Fortune 500 businesses. And we need someone to join us. As the Inbound Marketing Manager, you&#x2019;ll oversee and take part in the creation and delivery of recruiting content and social media content. The client will have all sorts of ideas, but your job is to be the consultant who helps them see the difference between the good and the bad, while adding your own ideas. Then you help build and deliver those flawlessly executed ideas week after week. You&#x2019;ll be accountable for getting things done well, and be given the resources to make it happen. This means you really need to understand the power of social media and content in the recruiting space, because you&#x2019;ll be explaining it to people on a regular basis, And you will need to make them fall in love with these ideas again and again. It&#x2019;s a strange job, where we value drive, flexibility and attitude over a resume full of big-name agency experience. So if all that sounds incredibly appealing, apply. In your cover letter, tell us something interesting about yourself, who you really are, and what you really are looking for. We might just be the right fit for you. Responsibilities: * Develop and execute comprehensive content strategies for recruitment clients * Executing and maintaining a social media program to stimulate traffic, brand awareness &amp; create buzz. * Execute organic strategies into social media utilizing Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, YouTube and other social media platforms. * Managing social media programs including but not limited to blogs, social networking applications and message boards. * Work extensively with account teams on understanding and building towards client strategic objectives. * Serving as a content and social media consultant and excel under deadline driven challenges while working with cross departments. * Generating metrics and benchmarks to effectively measure user behavior and satisfaction. * Creating, monitoring, and updating reports on social media activities daily, weekly, monthly * Ensuring TMP&#x2019;s TalentBrew software suite is utilized on a regular, strategic can consistent basis as applicable (as a destination, content pages, job content, etc.) * Keep abreast to latest development of social media best practices, trends, tools and recommend new strategies with meaningful measurements. To learn more about the TMP Chicago office and what we are working on- check out these links: https://www.tmp.com/tmp-office-spotlight-chicago</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>367905</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=367905&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>New York</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>NY</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Sr. Database Engineer</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>The Experience * 6+ years experience with SQL Server * 2+ years experience automating tasks with Python or Windows Powershell * Experience with both Windows and Linux Servers * Experience using source control systems such as Git * 2+ years experience with MongoDB desired * 2+ years experience with Elasticsearch desired * PostgreSQL or MySQL a plus * Experience with release automation tools a plus We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>The Role TMP is seeking an experienced database administrator with the versatility and expertise to succeed in a hybrid, high-performance data environment. The Sr. Database Engineer would be responsible for a variety of data systems from SQL Server to MongoDB to Elasticsearch. The contributor would spearhead projects involving automation and optimization of TMP's new and existing server environments. The role would require close collaboration with the development teams to design systems that meet the high demand and resilient service that our customers have grown to expect. This role provides opportunities to work with some of the newest technologies on the market. The Responsibilities * Database Monitoring Solutions * Database Development and Design Strategies using Best Practices * Release Automation Processes using SQL Server Data Tools (SSDT) * Patches and Upgrades * Server Resiliency, Fault Tolerance, and Disaster Recovery Strategies * Custom Automation for Data Integration and Administration * Performance Tuning and Server Optimizations * Research and Recommend New Technologies and Management Strategies for Database Systems * Compliance for Security Controls * Backup Management To learn more about what we are working on- check out this link: https://www.tmp.com/tmp-technology-jobs https://careers.stackoverflow.com/company/tmp-worldwide</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>368611</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=368611&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>New York</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>NY</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Sr Software Engineer - .Net, MVC</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>* BS or advanced degree in Computer Science, IT or related field * 6+ years of experience with product development and architecture of consumer software and applications * MVC 3.0 development; MVC 4.0 is a big plus * WinForms experience is a plus * Proven experience working with the latest technologies such as ASP.Net MVC, Entity Framework, Angular.js, Elastic Search, MongoDB and RabbitMQ * Expert knowledge of Agile, design and enterprise patterns * Knowledge of .Net 2.0+ and the C# Language * Expert knowledge of object-oriented programming * Knowledge of domain-driven design * Knowledge of test-driven development * Knowledge of aspect-oriented programming * Knowledge of SQL Server development and database design * Knowledge of UI patterns * Familiarity with source control, build processes, and continuous delivery * Experience guiding, coaching, and developing with other engineers * Excellent organizational and communication skills, both oral and written * Ability to influence and manage change * Ability to prepare and deliver presentations * Must possess a solid business sense to analyze IT viability and strategic vision * A wide breadth of technical expertise preferred * Occasional after-hours support may be required We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>When the world throws technology challenges at us, we eat them up. And then we ask for more. Welcome to life on the TMP technology team. Here, you&#x2019;ll work on our scalable, evolving platform, face tremendous software challenges, and work on projects for Fortune 100 clients. You'll be part of a fiercely collaborative technology team charged with creating digital solutions that are transforming the way employers and job seekers connect. That means contributing to high-traffic websites for a broad range of high-profile companies. Developing next-generation applications and products for some of the most recognized brands in the world. And actively supporting our diverse suite of best-in-class technologies. All this in an environment that constantly challenges you to push beyond boundaries and enhance your expertise&#x2014;with the support of a global team of industry experts. Sound like a fit for your talent and passion? Read on. Responsibilities: * Work with the latest technologies such as ASP.Net MVC, Entity Framework, Angular.js, Elastic Search, MongoDB and RabbitMQ * Develop next-generation web applications and products * Participate in all phases of the software engineering life cycle * Provide technical troubleshooting and debug support * Develop and implement new products and provide information and support when required * Evaluate new design proposals, and investigate and recommend solutions and process improvements that deliver greater efficiency or performance benefits * Ensure that necessary technical documentation is maintained in an appropriate manner To learn more about TMP Software Development and what we are working on- check out these links: https://www.tmp.com/tmp-technology-jobs Stack Overflow page: https://careers.stackoverflow.com/company/tmp-worldwide</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>373431</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=373431&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY>Canada</JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>Toronto</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>ON</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Director, New Business Development - HR Sector</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>* Must have a strong business network and relationships within the HR Sector - Senior HR and Talent Acquisition professionals (CHRO/SVP/VP/DIR) * Bachelor&#x2019;s Degree preferred * 7-10 years&#x2019; outside experience selling enterprise solutions, in new business development utilizing a consultative sales approach * Experience in the HR Sector required such as software, training and recruiting a must * Experience in advertising or related experience preferred * Comfortable working with and building relationships at all levels most importantly senior executives * Motivated, organized, energized and positive attitude * Strong probing and listening skills * Dynamic presentation and public speaking skills * Excellent written communications * Display strong closing techniques throughout the sales cycle * Strong networking capabilities * Proficiency with MS Office suite We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>We are redefining how companies around Toronto area and across Canada position themselves as employers of choice by using digital tools to help them attract, engage and retain the best talent in the market. You bring a proven expertise and passion for acquiring new clients and you have proven success in cold calling, sales pitches, creating presentation material, strategic planning, and general business development. You are a sales hunter who can tell a compelling story to senior HR and Talent Acquisition leaders using your influence and skills at relationship building. TMP Worldwide is growing fast and you will have an opportunity to make a real difference in the growth of our business and specifically here in the Toronto area. As Director, New Business Development for our Toronto office you will: * Develop and execute a sales and marketing plan on how you will achieve your goals and objectives * Engage Fortune 500 organizations and build relationships with primarily Senior HR and Talent Acquisition professionals and where appropriate with HRIS and Communications Leaders * Be a credible subject matter expert regarding trends in employer brand, recruitment marketing and advertising (new, digital, social, search media) * Formulate and answer request for proposals (RFPs); liaise and collaborate with RFP team * Work with local and cross-border teams to capitalize on their expertise for solution presentations and proposals * Conduct research on new customer prospects and their competitors by using online tools to identify opportunities to create prospect conversations * Influence prospect decision making by maintaining strong knowledge of current product and service offering to effectively articulate and align TMP&#x2019;s solution to the prospective customers&#x2019; needs * Work collaboratively with client development to seamlessly transition new customers to their dedicated Client Strategist or Account Director * Maintain expertise of industry and competitors to better understand TMP&#x2019;s value and differentiators in our market * Regularly attend networking events and conferences to promote TMP and your brand * Attend division meetings, calls and knowledge sessions * Coordinate and manage essential trade shows in assigned territory * Deliver on administrative responsibilities such as activity and pipeline reporting on a weekly and monthly basis</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>373954</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=373954&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>Chicago</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>IL</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Associate Media Planner</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>Requirements: * 0-1 year experience with print and online media negotiating, planning and buying; web/media analytics and reporting * Critical thinker with excellent MS Office product suite skills who can present complex concepts, media recommendations and data results in a clear and effective manner (PPT and Excel expertise a must) * The ability to manage multiple priorities in an ever-changing environment and meet tight deadlines * Be a self-starter who can work independently as well as part of a team * Strong written and verbal communication, organization, negotiation and troubleshooting skills * Knowledge and understanding of social media platforms and their respective participants.) and how they can be deployed in different scenarios * Familiarity with various interactive mediums including: websites, banners, mobile, etc. * Experience using comScore and 3rd party recommendation engines a plus We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>As an Associate Media Planner, you&#x2019;ll be responsible for assisting in the development media plans that recognize opportunities and recommending appropriate recruitment advertising solutions for the client. This position joins a team that is focused on results and works together to solve problems. Responsibilities: * Work directly with account team to understand overall client business and hiring objectives by function and location * Use client knowledge and a variety of tools to make solid on and offline media recommendations; build and deliver integrated media plans to achieve these goals * Work closely with media to negotiate packages to offer the best value to clients * Analyze the results and make optimization recommendations while the media is live and use empirical data to improve results for the next buying cycle * Ability to manage multiple plans across multiple markets in the US * Tell the full media story of the campaign lifecycle from inception through optimization to results, and do so in a client-facing, consultative manner * Evaluate new advertising opportunities * Market and demographic research * Ad hoc media research, such as one-off media packages that are not part of the plan * Ad placement, Insertion Orders (I.O.s) and contacting media To learn more about the TMP Chicago office and what we are working on- check out these links: https://www.tmp.com/tmp-office-spotlight-chicago</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>374860</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=374860&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>Chicago</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>IL</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Campaign Manager &#x2013; Programmatic Media</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>Requirements: * Bachelor&#x2019;s degree with a technical or business major. * 2-3 years of professional experience with at least 1 year of RTB/programmatic buying experience. * Advanced-level knowledge of Search Engine Marketing (SEM) * Proven technical knowledge to understand how to utilize our tech stack to design and optimize campaigns. Required Qualities/Skills * A motivated self-starter with the ability to work autonomously as well as collaboratively with other groups in the organization. * Superior logic and communication skills to present complex concepts and data analyses in a clear and effective manner. * Ability to manage multiple priorities in a fast-paced, ever changing environment. Preferred Experience/Skills: * Experience with multiple ad technologies and platforms: DSPs/DMPs/Ad Exchanges/Web Analytics. * Experience as an ad trafficker with DoubleClick or Atlas * Experience managing campaigns that have global reach and target non-English content or native speakers. * Expert user of Microsoft Excel. Experience with designing, configuring, automating custom reports from within the program. * Expert level knowledge of tagging and tracking methodology. * Other technical knowledge: HTML, JavaScript, SQL, R, Python. We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>Are you a technologist? Can you quickly interpret data to derive insights, and then turn those insights into action? If so, then let&#x2019;s talk! Here at TMP we do amazing things and can solve virtually any recruiting challenge with our software, technology and service solutions. At the center of it all is the revolutionary TalentBrew Software Platform &#x2013; powering TalentBrew 360, our proprietary programmatic media solution, along with a wide range of other solutions that simplify every aspect of the recruiting process. If you&#x2019;re not familiar with our industry, think ecommerce. Except instead of products, the inventory is jobs. With an impressive client roster, including more than 25% of the Fortune 100, we currently house over 2 million jobs, and last year alone we had more than 250 million visitors to our sites. Everything you do will help people around the world connect with careers and help fuel the global economy. This is the ever-changing world of candidate recruitment. And this is where your programmatic media management skills will be leading the way, making the connection. Responsibilities: * Manage all aspects of strategy and execution for biddable media on behalf of our clients. Day-to-day operations include campaign setup, ad trafficking, troubleshooting, QA, and campaign optimization. * Leverage our proprietary software and partner platforms to execute programmatic campaigns and to track and manage a comprehensive library of audiences for strategic use across channels and strategies. * Work beyond the core programmatic duty to also focus on other biddable media such as search engines, social platforms and job aggregator platforms. * Work closely with the account management and analytics teams to continuously improve campaign performance through detailed optimization and budget management to meet aggressive campaign goals and objectives. * Effectively collaborate and manage relationships both internally and externally with partner agencies, vendors, internal teams, and other stakeholders to ensure alignment and program effectiveness. * Collaborate with team members to Identify process inefficiencies and ways to improve operations workflow by providing feedback and input on new processes. To learn more about the TMP Chicago office and what we are working on- check out these links: https://www.tmp.com/tmp-office-spotlight-chicago</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>375319</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=375319&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>New York</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>NY</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>DevOps Engineer</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>* Expert knowledge of Citrix Netscaler * Expert knowledge of Cisco Routers/Firewall * 7+ years of hands on experience designing and administering networks * 7+ years experience administering VMWare * Strong knowledge of Powershell and Python * 7+ years of hands on experience with Windows and Linux server environments * Experience with CDN technologies We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>TMP is looking for a talented, seasoned, responsible, DevOps Engineer with a proven track record in network design, administration, and devops support. This role will be responsible for all network configuration and architectural decisions. Expert level knowledge of Citrix Netscalers and Cisco Routers/Firewalls a must. Knowledge and experience with multiple VMWare hosts and advanced configuration a must. The Senior Devops/Network Engineer will also play a lead role in automating many IT infrastructure components for both Linux and Windows in Python and Powershell. This role will be given the freedom to architect and optimize the network, as well as experiment with different monitoring and automation tools. Experience configuring/administrating any of the following a plus: MongoDB, Redis, Elastic Search, AWS, CI, Release Automation, CDN technologies (Akamai, MaxCDN), Orion Solarwinds, SQL Server Responsibilities: * Strategize, architect and build infrastructure that's appropriate for TMP&#x2019;s complex business. * Set and improve design standards for IT. * Represent IT interests and needs across diverse business groups, and prioritize workloads. * Collaborate across cross-functional teams and lead design processes for tactical and strategic initiatives. * Develop and manage capacity planning models to meet marketing forecasts. * Manage vendor relationships; keep abreast of vendor product roadmaps as well as industry best of breed technologies. * Configure, maintain, and administer Cisco Routers, Firewalls, and Citrix Netscaler. * Provide leadership for other members of the IT staff. To learn more about TMP Software Development and what we are working on- check out these links: https://www.tmp.com/tmp-technology-jobs Stack Overflow page: https://careers.stackoverflow.com/company/tmp-worldwide</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>376874</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=376874&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY>Germany</JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>Hamburg</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Account Director - Digital Strategy</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>Requirements: * BS/BA or equivalent experience required * 5+ years experience in Advertising/Marketing/PR client service * Must have experience developing and presenting custom digital solutions within a digital marketing, PR, and/or advertising agency environment * A demonstrated passion for search, social and mobile solutions and knowledge of how to leverage each to achieve marketing goals * Superior client service and demonstrated ability to grow internal and external client relationships * An understanding of the impact of social media across all digital marketing channels (and the ability to discuss the ROI of social media campaigns) * Deep understanding of the direction the digital landscape is going and a passion for all things digital * Demonstrated passion for technology and its use in driving revenue, client satisfaction and efficiency. * Flexibility to accommodate change and thrive amid ambiguity. * Exceptional communication skills (both written and verbal) and openness to providing feedback to help iterate the business. * Success in presenting strategic solutions and POVs that demonstrate thought leadership, and engage across social media * The ability to translate clients&#x2019; goals and objectives into actionable &amp; measurable digital marketing programs * Knowledge and understanding of social media platforms and their respective participants (Facebook, LinkedIn, YouTube, Twitter, etc.) and how they can be deployed in different scenarios * Should have strong understanding of interactive strategy, design, production and project management as well as tactics to leverage social media * Proven ability to solution sell and track record for closing digital business * Strong interpersonal, customer service, presentation, organizational and problem-solving skills * Strong self-discipline and time management skills. * Proven ability to understand customer needs and translate needs into solutions * Ability to balance revenue, client satisfaction and operational responsibilities while meeting deadlines * Strong knowledge of Excel, PowerPoint and other MS Office tools. * Strong quantitative and analytical skills. We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>Are you passionate about all aspects of digital advertising and providing clients with robust solutions and experiences that help them achieve their business objectives? Are you a driven and engaged professional who derives energy and creativity from working in a close-knit team environment? Big-picture thinking. Charismatic leadership. Long-term relationship building. That's what we expect from an Account Director- Digital Strategy at TMP. Here, you'll be part of a forward-thinking team charged with developing creative solutions that are transforming the way employers and job seekers connect. That means spearheading multi-pronged search, social and mobile marketing campaigns for a diverse suite of global organizations. Being the ambassador of our best-in-class technologies and digital capabilities to some of the most recognized companies in the world. And collaborating with people in every area and at every level of our organization on high-impact, enterprise-wide projects. All this in an environment that constantly challenges you to push beyond boundaries and enhance your expertise&#x2014;with the support of a global team of industry experts. Sound like a fit for your talent and passion? Read on. Responsibilities: * Monitor and manage all aspects of daily client performance * Act as the primary point of contact for assigned clients; escalate, track and solve client issues * Own the digital strategy for key client(s) * Support your region in achieving digital revenue goals by building strategic and creative digital marketing programs for clients, including Search, Social, Mobile and other Digital components * Introduce and evangelize our digital capabilities, emphasizing Search, Social and Mobile innovation * Lead agency thought leadership on social media channels * Develop in-depth knowledge of the industry and client business needs * Partner with Sales in pre-sales engagement work including developing proposals and campaign strategies that tie tightly with each client&#x2019;s media plans. * Drive established goals across relevant KPIs and balance business yield focused with client desired metrics. * Identify opportunities for performance improvement and upsell. * Working as a member of an account team to identify client needs and address them with strategic recommendation of TMP digital products and services * Maintain strong active relationships with key client stakeholders at both senior and mid-management levels; act as the primary point of contact for assigned clients * Comfortable and effective in complex project environments, and working with both long-range and short-term business objectives and management of multiple stakeholders * Interpreting and analyzing results data to improve client ROI * Delivering formal and informal presentations to clients as well as internal team members * Limited travel to sales / client offices or events may be required. To learn more about TMP Account Services and what we are working on- check out this link: https://www.tmp.com/client-services</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>377014</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=377014&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>New York</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>NY</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Art Director- NYC</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>Please include design samples or a link to your portfolio. * B.A. degree from four-year college or university (preferably in Graphic Design, Digital Design, Advertising or a related field). * 5 &#x2013; 8 years of graphic design experience incorporating both print and digital projects (agency experience preferred) * Strong visual sense with ability to execute to vision in Adobe InDesign, Photoshop, Illustrator, QuarkXPress and Keynote/PowerPoint on the Mac platform * Solid Understanding of web design principles including responsive/adaptive design, user experience &amp; accessibility as well as traditional prepress and production * Knowledge of web animation, CSS, HTML, JavaScript or other programming skills are an asset but not required as is additional experience with video editing, animation or rendering packages * Excellent listening and communications skills with the ability to pay strict attention to detail while juggling several complex projects * Strong interpersonal skills with a focus on relationship building and customer service We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>Unbridled creativity. Wicked smarts. Positive vibes. That&#x2019;s what we expect from an Art Director at TMP. Here, you'll be part of an integrated creative department charged with creating soup-to-nuts solutions that are transforming the way employers and job seekers connect. That means building powerful, authentic employer brands. Conceptualizing and executing robust recruitment campaigns. And creating smart, striking and targeted designs across a wide variety of digital and traditional media. All this in an environment that constantly challenges you to push beyond boundaries and enhance your expertise&#x2014;with the support of a global team of industry experts. We want to see concepts that make us go all goose-fleshy. We want to see artwork and layouts that move us to quiet tears. And we want your next idea to be even better. Sound like your bag? Read on. An Art Director leads the creative department&#x2019;s visual design aesthetic across digital, traditional and social advertising, marketing and promotional material. Working in tandem with a copywriter and under the direction of an ACD or CD, the Art Director helps lead the concepting and visualization of all agency work and gives direction to junior team members. Responsibilities * Work with project managers, digital strategists, producers and account service team members to help define client challenges and goals and to develop strategic and creative solutions that meet those goals * In partnership with Copywriters and ACDs/CDs, participate (and at times lead) creative concepting sessions in an effort to deliver industry-defining work across all media * Lead the department in translating concepts into fresh, cutting-edge and effective visual designs for digital, social, mobile and traditional media channels while leveraging existing assets and/or creating/sourcing new ones * Direct and manage the design output of junior team members, contracted illustrators and photographers as well as helping to manage ongoing departmental production needs * Continually grow, learn and experiment with new and innovative ways in which to solve client problems, and how to turn those solutions into innovative, dynamic creative executions * Present concepts internally to CDs and account/sales teams and actively participate in client calls and meetings with an eye toward building and strengthening relationships * Conduct ongoing research to help formulate ideas and drive effective creative while staying ahead of best practices, trends and new innovations in design, content generation/development and technology * Mentor and train junior members of the team in an effort to help them grow and reach their career goals within the agency</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>372175</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=372175&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>San Francisco</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>CA</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Digital Strategist</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>Requirements: * Bachelor&#x2019;s degree * Must have 3-5 years of experience developing and presenting custom digital solutions within a digital marketing, PR, and/or advertising agency environment * A demonstrated passion for search, social and mobile solutions and knowledge of how to leverage each to achieve marketing goals * Demonstrated experience building and executing digital/social media campaigns across social media platforms and emerging social networks/technologies * Strong knowledge of user-generated content, web video, and viral marketing on the web. * An understanding of web/campaign analytics, including usage of various analytics tools and software programs * An understanding of the impact of social media across all digital marketing channels (and the ability to discuss the ROI of social media campaigns) * Strong understanding of digital strategy, design, production and project management as well as tactics to leverage social media * Deep understanding of the direction the digital landscape is going and a passion for all things digital * The ability to translate clients&#x2019; goals and objectives into actionable and measurable digital marketing programs * Superior client service and demonstrated ability to grow internal and external client relationships * Proven ability to solution sell and track record for closing digital business * Superior written and verbal communication, interpersonal, organizational, public speaking, and customer service skills * Knowledge of digital and traditional media We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>Big-picture thinking. Charismatic leadership. Long-term relationship building. That's what we expect from a Digital Strategist at TMP. Here, you'll be part of a forward-thinking team charged with developing creative solutions that are transforming the way employers and job seekers connect. That means spearheading multi-pronged search, social and mobile marketing campaigns for a diverse suite of global organizations. Being the ambassador of our best-in-class technologies and digital capabilities to some of the most recognized companies in the world. And collaborating with people in every area and at every level of our organization on high-impact, enterprise-wide projects. All this in an environment that constantly challenges you to push beyond boundaries and enhance your expertise&#x2014;with the support of a global team of industry experts. Sound like a fit for your talent and passion? Read on. To learn more about TMP Digital Strategy and what we are working on- check out this link: https://www.tmp.com/digital-strategist-inside-scoop-what-to-read-before-you-apply Responsibilities: * Own the digital strategy for key client(s) * Support your region in achieving digital revenue goals by building strategic and creative digital marketing programs for clients, including Search, Social, Mobile and other Digital components * Work with the account and creative teams to guide the development and presentation of more complex, innovative and targeted digital solutions * Introduce and evangelize our digital capabilities, emphasizing Search, Social and Mobile innovation * Lead agency thought leadership on social media channels * Support Business Development staff with creative and strategic outlines as part of the RFP or proposal process * Help secure business by educating prospective clients on TMP&#x2019;s comprehensive digital offering * Stay up-to-date with Search, Social, and Mobile trends and innovations * Analyze metrics data to make recommendations that will increase client ROI * Deliver formal and informal presentations to help win and educate clients, prospects and internal teams * Develop written documentation such as proposals, presentations and client case studies</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>372301</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=372301&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>New York</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>NY</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Infrastructure Technical Lead</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>* Bachelor&#x2019;s degree in computer science or related field (MIS/CIS) or equivalent experience * MSCE and CCNA (or other Cisco certifications) are highly desired. ITIL also desirable. * Hands-on experience with Cisco, Juniper, or Extreme network equipment. * Requires a minimum of 5 years&#x2019; experience in network and server management as well as some experience leading technical engineers. * In-depth knowledge supporting and deploying Windows servers (2008/2012), VMWare, and Active Directory. * Must demonstrate real-world engineering expertise, problem solving, and analytical skills. * Strong interpersonal, customer service, and communications skills * Must be flexible to changing business requirements and the demands of a client-driven agency culture. We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>Working within the global technology Infrastructure team, the Infrastructure Technical Lead will lead technical engineers in the administration, implementation, and operational support of TMP&#x2019;s network and server infrastructure. This is a very hands-on position. We are looking for someone with ideas to help guide TMP as we continue to improve and globalize our systems and support structure. A sed TMP offers an exciting and fast-paced environment with growth and learning opportunities. TMP has locations in the US, Canada, Europe, and the Far East. The right candidate will have the opportunity to participate in all planning and implementation for all aspects of Technology Infrastructure and to expand upon their current skill set. This role will ensure that all TMP corporate systems and services satisfy the business requirements for high availability and performance. . Responsibilities: * Oversee the management and configuration of our corporate network devices and server strategy. Contribute to the global technical roadmap,. * Ensure proper network connectivity, availability, and performance between our offices (US and international) as well as within our datacenter. * Manage projects and initiatives related to server virtualization, server and network operations, documentation, and disaster recovery / business continuity. * Work with US and global technical resources and office managers to ensure technology requirements are met, including business applications, data backups, and DR planning. * Support of network devices (Cisco, Extreme, VoIP, VLANs) * Participate in office moves, coordinate networking and file server tasks. * Work with our datacenter provider to ensure proper SLAs are met. * Collaborate with our desktop support and business applications teams to handle escalated support issues and implementation of new systems. * Contribute to the IT team&#x2019;s policies and procedures. To learn more about TMP Software Development and what we are working on- check out these links: https://www.tmp.com/tmp-technology-jobs Stack Overflow page: https://careers.stackoverflow.com/company/tmp-worldwide</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>378736</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=378736&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>McLean</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>VA</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Sales Assistant</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>Requirements: * Bachelors Degree and at least 1 year working experience in a similar position * The ability to communicate clearly, concisely, and effectively both verbally and in writing * Strong interpersonal skills and the ability to build trusted and collaborative relationships at all levels * Strong analytical skills and the ability to interact with internal/external partners to solve problems and achieve sales goals * Must have strong PowerPoint skills as well as strong knowledge of MS Word and MS Excel * Organizational skill to include ability to handle multiple priorities and demonstrate good judgment * High Energy and a Great work Ethic are a must We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>Do you thrive in a competitive environment? We offer that type of environment where you will use a combination of your ingenuity, existing systems and some additional ones that you may have a hand in developing to support our new business efforts. You will partner with existing new business professionals to identify prospects and participate in the development and delivery of custom solutions in the talent management and acquisition field. If you have a proven track-record for supporting a sales effort, including answering product and service questions and assisting in acquiring new customers and are passionate about building strong and trusting relationships at all levels of an organization. If you have a natural ability and genuine desire to understand organizational recruitment goals and challenges and want to help build impactful digital solutions to address these needs, then we have the type of environment where your skills can make a difference with the opportunity to expand and develop your career. TMP Worldwide is growing fast and you will have an opportunity to make a real difference in the growth of our business in a collaborative environment. Responsibilities: * Develop and maintain sales reports for Business Development team. * Provide support for local RFP responses, product and financial proposals, partner agreements and NDA&#x2019;s. * Provide support and open communications to agency personnel and sales team. * Help schedule and coordinate internal planning meetings. * Assist in managing sales database input and generating reports for pipeline review. * Ability to produce PowerPoint presentations at a high level. * Enter opportunities and contacts into corporate CRM tool and assist Business * Development team in updating information in a real-time environment. * Provide general ad-hoc administrative support as and when needed by the team.</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>379626</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=379626&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>Waltham</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>MA</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Paid Spring Internship - Account Services</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>Requirements: * Currently enrolled in a degree-seeking program at an accredited college or university entering your Junior or Senior year, ideally in a Business Administration program with an emphasis in Marketing * Proficiency with basic computer programs (Mac platform) * 2-3 years of course work or experience * &#xad;&#xad;&#xad;&#xad;Ability to work a maximum of 20 hours per week * Positive, proactive &amp; energetic attitude, strong work ethic &amp; highly dependable * Exceptional communication skills (both written and verbal) and openness to providing feedback to help iterate the business. * Strong interpersonal, customer service, presentation, organizational and problem-solving skills * Strong self-discipline and time management skills. * Able to take direction * Self &#x2013;motivated. We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>Are you looking for a career in &#xad;&#xad;&#xad;&#xad;Advertising? Are you interested in seeing what a full service digital advertising agency work experience would be like? If so TMP Worldwide Advertising &amp; Communications, LLC is the place for you! We are looking for interns in the Advertising field to work closely with our Client Development department. This highly selective program offers participants an opportunity to explore the fundamental elements of the digital advertising industry within a leading digital advertising agency environment. We aim to cultivate our interns&#x2019; skill set across the business spectrum through hands-on learning, rotations, interaction with senior management, presentations and work related projects. Program Structure: * Experiential learning environment * Learning objectives are coordinated with projects and supervisory feedback to enhance your understanding of business responsibilities * E-Learning online instruction is combined with hands-on experiences to augment learning * Interaction with our experts to gain greater insight into the multitude of career opportunities * Increased understanding of the importance of coordination between functional areas to deliver the best business results * Completion of a project presented to executives and other senior management to assist in understanding real world applications</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>
<VIPER_JOB>
  <JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>381346</JDTID_UNIQUE_NUMBER>
  <ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>02/24/2016</ASSIGNMENT_START_DATE>
  <OTHER_LOCATIONS/>
  <OTHER_CATEGORIES/>
  <COMPANY_URL>http://www.tmp.com</COMPANY_URL>
  <EDUCATION/>
  <EMAIL_FOR_RESUMES/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL>https://www.hirebridge.com/v3/application/JobApplyLogin.aspx?cid=6023&amp;bid=1&amp;jid=381346&amp;s=93f22a4b-7e8f-40f1-9d4d-e492f154187c</JOB_APPLY_URL>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_LIST/>
  <JOB_APPLY_URL_NAMES/>
  <JOB_CATEGORY/>

  <JOB_INDUSTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_COUNTRY/>
  <JOB_LOCATION_CITY>Dallas</JOB_LOCATION_CITY>
  <JOB_LOCATION_STATE>TX</JOB_LOCATION_STATE>
  <JOB_LOCATION_ZIP/>
  <JOB_CONTACT_ADDRESS/>
  <JOB_SALARY/>
  <JOB_SALARY_FROM>25,000</JOB_SALARY_FROM>
  <JOB_SALARY_TO>125,000</JOB_SALARY_TO>
  <JOB_SHOW_CONTACT/>
  <JOB_STATUS>Contract to hire</JOB_STATUS>
  <JOB_TITLE>Account Director- Digital Strategy</JOB_TITLE>
  <JOB_TYPE/>
  <NOTES_FOR_INVOICE/>
  <NUMBER_TO_FILL/>
  <PO_NUMBER/>
  <QUALIFICATIONS>Requirements: * BS/BA or equivalent experience required * 5+ years experience in Advertising/Marketing/PR client service * Must have experience developing and presenting custom digital solutions within a digital marketing, PR, and/or advertising agency environment * A demonstrated passion for search, social and mobile solutions and knowledge of how to leverage each to achieve marketing goals * Superior client service and demonstrated ability to grow internal and external client relationships * An understanding of the impact of social media across all digital marketing channels (and the ability to discuss the ROI of social media campaigns) * Deep understanding of the direction the digital landscape is going and a passion for all things digital * Demonstrated passion for technology and its use in driving revenue, client satisfaction and efficiency. * Flexibility to accommodate change and thrive amid ambiguity. * Exceptional communication skills (both written and verbal) and openness to providing feedback to help iterate the business. * Success in presenting strategic solutions and POVs that demonstrate thought leadership, and engage across social media * The ability to translate clients&#x2019; goals and objectives into actionable &amp; measurable digital marketing programs * Knowledge and understanding of social media platforms and their respective participants (Facebook, LinkedIn, YouTube, Twitter, etc.) and how they can be deployed in different scenarios * Should have strong understanding of interactive strategy, design, production and project management as well as tactics to leverage social media * Proven ability to solution sell and track record for closing digital business * Strong interpersonal, customer service, presentation, organizational and problem-solving skills * Strong self-discipline and time management skills. * Proven ability to understand customer needs and translate needs into solutions * Ability to balance revenue, client satisfaction and operational responsibilities while meeting deadlines * Strong knowledge of Excel, PowerPoint and other MS Office tools. * Strong quantitative and analytical skills. We are an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.</QUALIFICATIONS>
  <RELOCATION>NO</RELOCATION>
  <SALARYTIME/>
  <TEXT>Are you passionate about all aspects of digital advertising and providing clients with robust solutions and experiences that help them achieve their business objectives? Are you a driven and engaged professional who derives energy and creativity from working in a close-knit team environment? Big-picture thinking. Charismatic leadership. Long-term relationship building. That's what we expect from an Account Director- Digital Strategy at TMP. Here, you'll be part of a forward-thinking team charged with developing creative solutions that are transforming the way employers and job seekers connect. That means spearheading multi-pronged search, social and mobile marketing campaigns for a diverse suite of global organizations. Being the ambassador of our best-in-class technologies and digital capabilities to some of the most recognized companies in the world. And collaborating with people in every area and at every level of our organization on high-impact, enterprise-wide projects. All this in an environment that constantly challenges you to push beyond boundaries and enhance your expertise&#x2014;with the support of a global team of industry experts. Sound like a fit for your talent and passion? Read on. Responsibilities: * Monitor and manage all aspects of daily client performance * Act as the primary point of contact for assigned clients; escalate, track and solve client issues * Own the digital strategy for key client(s) * Support your region in achieving digital revenue goals by building strategic and creative digital marketing programs for clients, including Search, Social, Mobile and other Digital components * Introduce and evangelize our digital capabilities, emphasizing Search, Social and Mobile innovation * Lead agency thought leadership on social media channels * Develop in-depth knowledge of the industry and client business needs * Partner with Sales in pre-sales engagement work including developing proposals and campaign strategies that tie tightly with each client&#x2019;s media plans. * Drive established goals across relevant KPIs and balance business yield focused with client desired metrics. * Identify opportunities for performance improvement and upsell. * Working as a member of an account team to identify client needs and address them with strategic recommendation of TMP digital products and services * Maintain strong active relationships with key client stakeholders at both senior and mid-management levels; act as the primary point of contact for assigned clients * Comfortable and effective in complex project environments, and working with both long-range and short-term business objectives and management of multiple stakeholders * Interpreting and analyzing results data to improve client ROI * Delivering formal and informal presentations to clients as well as internal team members * Limited travel to sales / client offices or events may be required. To learn more about TMP Account Services and what we are working on- check out this link: http://www.jobsattmp.com/live-digital</TEXT>
  <TRAVEL>Yes</TRAVEL>
</VIPER_JOB>

              </objects>